翻译：toto / Robert
DON'T FORGET THIS.
别忘了这个
THAT WAS A PRESENT FOR YOU.
那是给你的礼物
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE HOLDING ON TO IT.
拿着它让我觉得不舒服
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO WITH IT?
所以我应该拿它怎么办
THROW IT AWAY.
就扔掉咯
FINE.
好
Appropriate Behavior
伊朗式分手
WE WERE AN "IT" COUPLE.
我们总是万众瞩目的一对
NOT REALLY.
不是吧
LIKE WHEN WE'D GO TO PARTIES AND THERE WAS DANCING,
就像是我们去参加派对，那儿有人跳舞
WE'D START DANCING AND EVERYONE WOULD
我们也会开始跳 然后所有人
MAKE A CIRCLE AROUND US AND WATCH US DANCE.
都围在我们旁边 看着我们跳
OKAY.
好吧
OKAY, WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
你为什么不直接告诉我
WHAT YOU NEED, SHIRIN?
你到底需要什么呢，Shirin？
I NEED MY GIRLFRIEND BACK.
我想要我女朋友回心转意
DUDE, I REALLY THINK
我真的觉得
YOU JUST NEED TO MOURN THIS AND MOVE ON.
你需要从悲伤中走出来 向前看
I REALLY WANT TO EAT MY FEELINGS RIGHT NOW.
我是真的很难过
YOU KNOW WHAT?
你知道吗
I THINK THAT'S AN AMAZING IDEA.
我想到一个很棒的主意
WHY DON'T WE ORDER ALL THE FATTY, DISGUSTING FOODS
为什么我们不点一些以前克制着不吃的
WE NEVER LET OURSELVES EAT?
那些油腻恶心的食物呢？
OKAY.
好
HEY, GIRLS. HOW YOU DOIN' TODAY?
嘿 姑娘们 今天过得怎么样
HEY. FANTASTIC.
嘿 很棒
AND YOU?
你呢
UH, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
你叫什么名字
BRENDAN.
Brendan.
HEY, I'M CRYSTAL.
嘿 我叫Crystal
HEY, CRYSTAL.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU TODAY?
你们想要些什么？
UM, LET ME SEE.
啊，让我看看
I WOULD LOVE AN...
我想要
UNSWEETENED GLASS OF ICED TEA.
一杯不加糖的冰茶
NO PROBLEM.
好的
THANK YOU.
谢谢
AND CAN I JUST HAVE ONE OF THOSE COMPLIMENTARY MINTS
我就想要一些我在门口广告里看到的
I SAW BY THE ENTRANCE AND A GLASS OF ICE WATER
免费的薄荷叶和一杯
AND A LITTLE BIT OF LEMON IN THERE.
加少量柠檬的冰水
OKAY.
好的
THANK YOU SO MUCH.BRENDAN.
谢谢，Brendan
MMM, DELISH.
哎，真是美味啊
MMM, CAN'T WAIT.
哎，简直等不及了
I'M DEAD INSIDE.
我感觉整个人都死透了
CAN YOU TELL JUST BY LOOKING AT ME
你能透过我的眼睛
THAT I'M DEAD INSIDE?
看出来我死透了吗？
I REALLY THINK YOU HAD TO END IT.
我是真的觉得你得把这事给了结了
I MEAN, SHE WASN'T EVEN FUCKING YOU TOWARDS THE END.
我的意思是，她最后都不想和你做爱了
MAYBE IT WAS A PHASE.
也许那是阶段性的吧
THANKS, BRENDAN.
谢谢你，Brendan
HOW ABOUT "GIRAFFE"?
“长颈鹿”这个词怎么样
WHAT ABOUT "SAFE WORD"?
“安全词”呢？
LIKE THE WORD "SAFE WORD"AS OUR SAFE WORD?
就是把“安全词”作为我们的安全词
LET'S CUT OUT THE MIDDLEMAN,
考虑到如果忘记了安全词的后果
'CAUSE WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU FORGET YOUR SAFE WORD?
我们还不如直接一些
OKAY, THEN, THE SAFE WORD IS "SAFE WORD."
好吧，那安全词就是“安全词”了
GREAT. LET'S DO THIS.
好，那就这么办吧
WHAT'S THE SCENARIO?
现在是什么节奏？
I'M YOUR TAX AUDITOR.
我是你的税率审计员
OKAY.
好
MISS?
小姐
YES?
嗯？
CAN YOU PLEASE FILL OUT THIS FORM?
你能填一下这些表格吗？
ALL RIGHT.
可
MISS?
小姐
YES?
嗯？
I'VE BEEN A BAD SMALL-BUSINESS OWNER.
我是个失败的小商人
WHAT SEEMS TO BE THE PROBLEM?
怎么回事？
I DON'T HAVE ANY OF MY RECEIPTS
从六月到八月
FROM JUNE UNTIL AUGUST,
我收钱都没有开发票
AND I'M GONNA HAVE TO BE PUNISHED.
我觉得我需要被惩罚一下
THAT'S ACTUALLY EASILY REMEDIED.
这很好办
IF YOU'LL JUST FILL IN THE LARGER EXPENSES IN SECTION C
你就在C部分填上你的最大开支
AND CROSS-CHECK THEM WITH SECTION B.
在B部分反复核对
MAXINE.
Maxine
WHAT?
怎么了
YOU ARE KILLING THE SEXY.
你正在破坏情趣
I'M JUST--
我只是
I'M NOT INTO ROLE PLAY.
我不擅长角色扮演
THAT'S-- THAT'S OKAY.
好吧好吧
I'M VANILLA.
我是个无趣的人
DON'T SAY THAT.
别这么说
IT'S TRUE. I'M NOT KINKY.
真的，我玩不了角色扮演
HEY.
LOOK AT ME.
看着我
I LIKE VANILLA.
我就喜欢无趣的
I'M NOT REALLY IN THE MOOD.
我不是很有心情做这个
I'M SORRY.
对不起
IT'S OKAY.
没事
BANAL SEX SHOULDN'T START
从热恋过渡到平庸的性爱
UNTIL AT LEAST A YEAR INTO A RELATIONSHIP.
这个过程起码也得有一年才对啊
I MOVED IN TOO SOON.
我们同居得太快了
WHEN ARE YOU GOING BACK TO WORK?
你什么时候回去工作
I'M NOT.
我不回去了
NO!
为什么！
THE ONLY REASON THEY HIRED ME IN THE FIRST PLACE
他们雇用我的唯一的原因就是
IS 'CAUSE THEY WANTED
他们想雇一个
A MIDDLE EASTERN PERSON ON STAFF.
来自中东的人而已
NOW THAT YAVAH'S IN EDITORIAL,
现在Yavah调到了编辑部
EVERYONE'S GUSHING OVER HOW SYRIAN SHE IS.
每个人都滔滔不绝地讨论着她的行为举止是多么的叙利亚风格
I'M NOT LETTING YOU FALL INTO A BOTTOMLESS PIT
我不会让你现在坐在我的沙发上
OF DESPAIR AND UNEMPLOYMENT ON MY COUCH.
却掉入失业的悲伤无底洞
NOTHING BRINGS ME JOY.
没有什么东西能让我感到快乐了
WELL... I THINK THIS GUY I KNOW IS HIRING.
唔…有一个我认识的男人正在招工
LET ME TALK TO HIM.
让我跟他谈谈
AND ARE YOU GONNA GO LOOK
你待会儿想去看看吗？
AT THAT APARTMENT IN BUSHWICK LATER?
就在布许维克的公寓
I CAN'T. I HAVE TO GO SEE MY PARENTS.
不行，我得去看我父母
OH, MY GOD! CAN I COME?
天哪！我能去吗！
YOUR DAD IS SO HOT.
你爸爸超级性感
I JUST WANT TO, LIKE, PAINT HIM.
我只是想，画他，请他当模特
UGH, NO.
呃，不行
THAT IS EXACTLY WHY YOU CANNOT COME.
那就是你不能来的原因
SO, UH...
所以...
SO, IN THE AFTERNOON, I TOOK AN APPENDIX,
所以下午的时候我得到一个阑尾
AND I REWIRED IT ON THIS KID
并把它重装在一个
WHO HAD NO CONTROL OF HIS OWN URINE.
尿失禁的孩子身上
STOP.
别说了
WOW.
哇
NO, NO, NO, WE MADE HIM DRY.
不不不，他不再失禁了
BUT NOW HE HAS TO PEE OUT OF HIS BELLY BUTTON.
但是现在他得从肚脐眼撒尿了
PLEASE STOP.
请闭嘴
THIS IS FASCINATING. NOT WHILE WE'RE EATING.
那蛮有趣的，但不是在我们吃饭的时候
YEAH, IT CAN WAIT UNTIL AFTER, RIGHT?
那些不是可以留到饭后再讲吗？
OKAY.
好
DID YOU SEE ALI'S PICTURE
你有看Ali那副
OF THE SEX-REASSIGNMENT SURGERY?
关于变性手术的画吗？
NO, I DIDN'T, 'CAUSE I DELETED IT THE MINUTE
没，我没注意
I READ "INTESTINE VAGINA" IN THE SUBJECT.
我看见“国内阴道”这个字眼就立马把邮件删了
THEY'RE INTERESTING PICTURES.
里面有一些有趣的图
YEAH, THEY ARE.
是的吧
SHOW THEM.
展示一下
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
请别这样做
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
我真的不明白
HE HAD TO GO INTO UROLOGY.
为什么他要学泌尿学
IT'S BECAUSE HE LOVES THE PENISES SO MUCH.
那是因为他太爱鸡巴了
FUNNY, DAD.
哈哈哈
HERE YOU GO. CHECK IT OUT.
来，好好看看
UGH!
哦不！
OH, MY GOD.
天哪
WHAT?
怎么了
TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
好好看看咯
YOU'RE NOT EVEN LOOKING AT IT.
你都不看它
PLEASE PUT THAT AWAY.
请把它收起来
I DON'T WANT TO SEE IT.
我不想看
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO SEE IT.
她不想看
PUT IT AWAY.
快收起来
OKAY, SUIT YOURSELF.
好吧，随你便
LAYLI.
Layli
YES?
嗯？
ALI SAYS THAT YOU JUST STARTED YOUR FELLOWSHIP.
Ali说你刚刚开始读研究生
THAT'S RIGHT.
是的
PLASTIC SURGERY.
整形外科？
MM-HMM
嗯
ISN'T IT WEIRD, THOUGH?
这难道不奇怪吗
LIKE, HE'S DEALING
就是，他每天
WITH LIFE-AND-DEATH SITUATIONS EVERY DAY,
都在处理生死攸关的问题
AND THEN YOU'RE WITH THESE MIDDLE-AGED HOUSEWIVES
然后你就整天和那些没什么自信的
WITH LOW SELF-ESTEEM.
中年妇女在一起
LAYLI IS A PEDIATRIC
Layli是研究少儿
RECONSTRUCTIVE PLASTIC SURGEON.
重塑整形手术的
I ACTUALLY--UH, I SPECIALIZE
确切的说
IN BURN TREATMENT AND SKIN GRAFTING.
我专门研究烧伤皮肤移植问题的
COOL.
酷
I HEARD YOU ARE WORKING AT "THE BROOKLYN PAPER."
我听说你在布鲁克林报社工作
YEAH.
好吧
UM, I'M ACTUALLY THINKING
我其实在考虑
ABOUT TRANSITIONING INTO ANOTHER FIELD.
换一个工作
SO, LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
等等，如果我没理解错的话
YOU GOT A MASTERS IN JOURNALISM,
你得到了新闻学硕士学位
AND NOW YOU'RE GONNA DO JACK SHIT WITH IT?
现在你却不想要了，打算从零开始吗？
SHE CAN STILL USE HER DEGREE.
她的学位依然有用
SHE'S SO TALENTED.
她很聪明
THANK YOU.
谢谢
SHE WAS THE ONLY FRESHMAN IN HIGH SCHOOL
她可是唯一一个能够加入
WHO COULD SWIM ON THE VARSITY TEAM.
大学游泳代表队的高一学生
AND SHE DIDN'T EVEN TAKE LESSONS.
而且她根本没有系统地训练过
WOW, THAT'S A REAL RESUME BUILDER RIGHT THERE.
哇，这个在简历里会很显眼哦
YEAH, THIS BODY'S MADE FOR SWIMMING.
这个身体简直就是为游泳而生的
LOOK AT THESE SHOULDERS.
你看看这肩膀
THAT'S ENOUGH.
够了
THANK YOU.
谢谢
AND LOOK AT THOSE HANDS.
再看看这双手
PLEASE STOP.
别再说了
AREN'T THEY STUNNING?
这手太有魅力了
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL HANDS.
真的是很美丽的手
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD GET INTO HAND MODELING.
你应该去做手模的
AH.
呵呵
BUT I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW PEOPLE GET STARTED.
但我就是不知道人们怎么开始一份新工作
IT'S WHO YOU KNOW.
靠你的人脉
A MASTERS IN JOURNALISM, THAT'S HOW YOU GET STARTED.
就从一个新闻学硕士开始
I WOULD LITERALLY LIKE TO TALK ABOUT ANYTHING ELSE.
我们不能谈点别的吗？
OKAY, HOW'S YOUR LOVE LIFE?
好吧，那你的爱情事业如何了？
ANY BOYS WE SHOULD KNOW ABOUT?
有什么男孩可以带给我们看看的吗？
NO. NO BOYS AT ALL.
没 没有男朋友
OH, THANK GOD I DON'T HAVE TO GET MY SHOTGUN READY THEN.
哦感谢上帝 看来我还不需要急着把我的枪准备好
GOOD ONE, DAD.
爸爸 你真棒
OH, GOD.
天哪
KEN?
HEY.
GINNY.
SHIRIN.
不，我叫Shirin.
WHAT IS THAT? LIBYAN? ARMENIAN? ARGENTINEAN?
所以你是利比亚人？亚美尼亚人？阿根廷人？
IRANIAN.
伊朗人
OH, IRANIAN.
哦伊朗人
WOW. IRAN.
哇，伊朗
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT WHOLE SITUATION?
你是怎么看现在的形势的？
IT'S A MIXED BAG.
蛮复杂的
A LOT OF VERY GOOD-INTENTIONED PEOPLE
很多善意的人
DEALING WITH SOME DIFFICULT CIRCUMSTANCES.
在处理各种难题
YOU GET OVER THERE VERY OFTEN?
你经常到那儿去吗？
YEAH.
是的
ACTUALLY, I GO IN THE SUMMERS TO VISIT FAMILY.
事实上，夏天我会去那儿走走亲戚
WOW.
哦
OKAY, SO TELL ME,
所以，告诉我
WHAT IS THE SCENE LIKE IN TEHRAN?
德黑兰的情况如何？
I JUST READ THIS BIG ARTICLE
我刚刚在Vice杂志上读了一篇
ABOUT THE UNDERGROUND HIP-HOP SCENE IN "VICE."
关于地下嘻哈场景的文章
YEAH.SO, YOU'RE PART OF THAT?
所以你也是其中的一份子吗？
NO. UNFORTUNATELY, I SPEND MOST OF MY TIME IN IRAN
不，我在伊朗的大部分时间
WATCHING DISNEY VIDEOS WITH MY GRANDMOTHER
都用来和我祖母一起看迪士尼动画
WHILE SHE UNTANGLES JEWELRY.
她会一边看一边整理珠宝
YEAH, I GOT MYSELFSOME COFFEE.
哦，我给自己点了咖啡
DO YOU WANT SOMETHING TO DRINK?
你想来点喝的嘛？
NO, THANKS.
不 谢谢
I AM BUZZED ON SKUNK RIGHT NOW.
我现在就轻飘飘的了
NICE.
好吧
SO, CRYSTAL TELLS ME YOU ARE AN ARTIST.
Crystal告诉我你是一个艺术家
YES.
是的
YEAH, I AM.
是的，我是
YOU'RE A VIDEO ARTIST.
你是影像方面的艺术家
MM-HMM.
嗯
GREAT.
棒
SO, I DON'T KNOW WHAT CRYSTAL HAS TOLD YOU,
我不知道Crystal告诉了你什么
BUT I'M LOOKING FOR SOMEONE RELIABLE TO TAKE OVER
但我在找一个可靠的人去接管
AN AFTERSCHOOL FILMMAKING CLASS.
一个课外电影制作班
IT'S WITH A BUNCH OF KIDS, AND THEY'RE REALLY GREAT
给一群很棒的孩子上课
AND SO SMART AND, UH, JUST CREATIVE.
他们很聪明，很有创造力
AND REALLY,ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
说真的，你需要做的
IS JUST SHOW THEM HOW TO HOLD A CAMERA.
只是教他们如何用相机而已
I CAN DO THAT, YEAH.
我能做到
SO, WHAT IS YOUR SCHEDULE LIKE?
所以你的工作时间是？
COMPLETELY OPEN.
完全自由
PERFECT.
好极了
ALL RIGHT, WELL, MAY I SAY LET'S DO THIS?
好的，那我们开始干活？
OKAY.
好
GREAT.
很好
DON'T FUCK ME OVER.
别让我失望
OKAY.
好
YOU TOLD HIM I WAS A FILMMAKER?
你居然告诉他我是电影制作人？
YOU SAID YOU NEEDED A JOB.
是你说你需要一个工作
HOW DO YOU KNOW THIS GUY ANYWAY?
那你是怎么认识这个人的？
HE'S THAT INVESTMENT BANKER IN MY PARENTS' BUILDING
他是个投资银行家，跟我住一栋楼
I USED TO HOOK UP WITH IN HIGH SCHOOL.
高中时我们在一起过
OH, MY GOD.HE'S THAT GUY.
惹，原来就是这个家伙啊
YEAH, SO HE LOST HIS JOB, BECAME A STAY-AT-HOME DAD,
是的，他丢了工作，现在就做一个全职父亲
AND GOT INTO LIGHT DRUGS.
并且磕点药
GOOD FOR HIM.
挺适合他的
SO, DO YOU HAVE A LESSON PLAN?
所以你有教学计划吗？
WHAT IS THIS, GERMANY?
教学计划？我才没那么严谨
THEY'RE PARK SLOPE TEENS.
这就是群布鲁克林学生而已
I COULD LOCK 'EM IN A ROOM
我可以把他们锁在一个房间里
WITH A HALF-EATEN APPLE AND A TIC TAC
再放个啃了一半的苹果让他们随便拍
AND COME BACK TO THE "MONA LISA."
等家长来接的时候再装装样子就好了
WH-- WHY ARE WE STOPPING?
我们怎么停下了
OH, I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF SOMETHING.
我有些事情需要处理
YOU WAIT OUT HERE.
你在外面等着
NO, NO, NO, WAIT.
不不，等一下
OH, PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
别这么做
YOU SAID THAT NO AMOUNT OF WHOLESALE SPELT SUSHI
你说过，你凡是在这儿批发的寿司
WAS WORTH THE EMOTIONAL TOLL OF BEING HERE.
可全都是意气用事，完全不值啊！
SHE'S HERE ALL THE TIME.
但是Maxine一直在这里啊
THEY DON'T EVEN OFFER PAPER BAGS.
他们甚至连个纸袋都不给你
IT'S SURPRISING HOW, UH, LONELY IT GETS
一个人竟然能感觉这么孤独
WHEN YOU'RE SINGLE AGAIN,
当他回归单身
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU LIVE WITH SOMEONE.
尤其是，他曾和别人一起生活过
YOU GET SO USED TO THEIR HABITS
早已习惯另一半的爱好
AND THEIR LIFESTYLE AND THEIR SMELLS,
他们的生活习惯，他们的气味
BUT, UM, I REALLY JOINED THE CO-OP
我真的加入了她在的那个消费合作社
TO SPEND TIME WITH HER,'CAUSE, LET'S BE HONEST,
就为了能跟她在一起，但说实话
IT'S NOT THE MOST PLEASANT PLACE TO WORK IN THE WORLD.
那儿并不舒服
BUT IF I REALLY WANT MAXINE BACK IN MY LIFE,
但如果我真的希望Maxine回到我身边
I'M GONNA HAVE TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES,
我会愿意付出任何代价
AND THAT MEANS GETTING BACK ONTO HER CO-OP SHIFT,
那就意味着我要去参加她在的合作社
AND THAT'S WHERE YOU COME IN.
当然，也就是你这里
IT-- IT SAYS IN YOUR FILE
根据你的档案
THAT YOU HAVEN'T WORKED A SHIFT IN FOUR MONTHS.
你已经四个月没参与工作了
EXTENUATING CIRCUMSTANCES.
特殊情况，情有可原啊
I'VE HAD A VERY BROKEN HEART.
那段时间我真的很心碎
LOOK, ALL MEMBERS ARE ENTITLED
诚然，所有的成员在失职之后
TO ONE FREE PASS AFTER A DELINQUENCY,
都有一次被原谅的机会
BUT I CANNOT GET YOU ONTO HER SHIFT.
但我还是不能把你调去她那边
IT'S ALL BOOKED.
满员了
I'M SORRY, I DIDN'T CATCH YOUR NAME.
对不起，你的名字是？
JACKIE.
HI, JACKIE.
UM...
THE LAST TIME I CHECKED, THIS IS A COOPERATIVE.
我知道这是个合作社
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD AND COOPERATE WITH ME,
既然这样，你就帮我个忙，和我合作一下
AND I'LL COOPERATE WITH YOU.
我也会好好工作，这样不好吗？
BUT HOW DO YOU GET THEM SO CURLY?
你是怎么把它们弄得那么卷的？
LET'S GO.
我们走吧
IT WAS SO NICE MEETING YOU.
很高兴认识你
SHIRIN TOLD ME YOU'RE AN ARTIST.
Shirin告诉我你是一个艺术家
LANDSCAPING OR PORTRAITS?
是擅长景物还是人像呢？
I SPECIALIZE IN EXPERIMENTAL INSTALLATIONS,
我擅长搞实验性的装置艺术
AND JACQUES IS CURRENTLY FOCUSING ON SANDCASTLE WORK
Jacques最近在忙他的沙雕
INTEGRATING FOUND OBJECTS.
把他找的小东西组合成艺术品
WE'RE DONE WITH THE BOXES.
我们搬完箱子了
I'M COMING.
我就来
IT WAS SO NICE MEETING YOU.
很高兴认识你
THERE'S NO TOILET PAPER.
洗手间里没有厕纸了
HEY, YOU GUYS CAN GO.
你们可以走了
I FEEL LIKE I'M 17
我感觉我只有17岁
AND YOU'RE MOVING ME BACK INTO COLLEGE.
你们让我觉得我还是像个大学生似的
I WISH.
我倒希望如此
THAT DORM WAS MUCH NICER.
大学宿舍都比这儿强
THIS IS WHAT IT IS TO FIND A PLACE
我就是想在布鲁克林
ON SHORT NOTICE IN BROOKLYN.
找一个僻静的地方而已
AT LEAST YOU HAVE A SEXY ROOMMATE.
至少你有一个性感的室友
FELICIA? I FIND HER A BIT TERRIFYING.
你是说Felicia吗？ 我觉得她有点可怕
NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT THE BOY-- JACQUES.
不，我是说Jacques
YOUR NEW ROOMMATES ARE FREAKS.
你的新室友们全是怪胎
HEY, IS THIS HOW YOU SAY HELLO?
嘿，你就这么打招呼吗
HI.
CAN WE TELL HER?
我们能告诉她了吗？
TELL ME WHAT?
告诉她什么？
I'M PROPOSING TO LAYLI.
我打算向Layli求婚的事啊
WHY?
……啥
HEY.
SHIRIN.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU SHOULDN'T DO IT.
我不是说你不该这么做
IT'S JUST...
只是
HE'S VERY YOUNG.
他还年轻
HE'S 33.
他已经33岁了
I WAS ONLY 19 WHEN I MARRIED YOUR FATHER.
我嫁给你爸爸的时候还只有19岁
WELL, THIS ISN'T THE ISLAMIC REPUBLIC OF IRAN, MOM.
妈妈 这里又不是伊朗
DO YOU SEE A HIJAB ON MY HEAD?
你看见我包头巾了吗？
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
你有什么毛病？
NOTHING.
我很好
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A BRAT.
你太无理取闹了
STOP IT.
住嘴
YOU'RE BRINGING A LOT OF NEGATIVE ENERGY
你给我的新家
INTO MY NEW HOME.
带来了太多的负能量
OH, THIS IS NOT A HOME.
这哪能算个家
THIS IS A REFUGEE CAMP.
就根本就是一个难民营
SERIOUSLY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
你到底想干什么
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT A COOL BROOKLYN LOFT LOOKS LIKE.
你根本不知道一个布鲁克林房间有多酷
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
我是真的不懂
WHY YOU LEFT YOUR OLD APARTMENT.
为什么你要搬家
THE NEIGHBORHOOD WAS SO MUCH BETTER.
原来那些邻居都很棒
IT GOT TOO EXPENSIVE.
那里太贵了
WE WOULD HAVE HELPED YOU.
我们会资助你啊
THIS IS MY NEW HOME, AND I LOVE IT.
这里是我新家，而且我很喜欢
OKAY.
好吧
ALI, COME. HELP ME IN THE KITCHEN.
Ali，到厨房来帮忙
OKAY, BUT I'M NOT TOUCHING ANYTHING.
好，但我不会碰任何东西的
I'M SURE THE GIRL WHO LET ME IN HAS HEP C.
我敢肯定，外边那个女怪胎有丙型肝炎
DAD?
爸爸
YEAH?
嗯？
I'M WORRIED ABOUT ALI.
我很担心Ali
I THINK HE'S JUMPING INTO MARRIAGE
他对婚姻太不谨慎了
BECAUSE HE THINKS HE HAS TO.
因为他觉得他不得不这么做
管好你自己的事
HE'S GOT CLASSIC OLDER CHILD SYNDROME.
他得了标准的长子综合症
HE'LL DO ANYTHING TO MAKE YOU AND MOM HAPPY.
他会做任何事来让你和妈妈开心
SHE HAS NO GOALS OR ASPIRATIONS.
她没有目标没有动力
SHE TAKES NOTHING SERIOUSLY.
她对任何事都不在意
SHE'S BECOMING A LOSER.
她就是个失败者
LOWER YOUR VOICE.
小声点
SHE HAS THIS, LIKE, YOUNGER CHILD THING.
她就像是一个不懂事的小孩
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU NEED TO BE ON TOP OF THAT.
我告诉你，你真的要加把劲了，多劝劝她
YOU DON'T THINK I'M DOING MY BEST?
你以为我没努力吗
SHE'S NOT EASY.
她也不容易
HE'S, LIKE, BURYING HIS EMOTIONS
他把自己真正的情感
DEEP BENEATH THE SURFACE,
深深地掩埋在心底
AND, LIKE, ONE DAY, HE COULD PULL A GUN
某一天，他会爆发，甚至会掏出枪
ON HIS COWORKERS.
对准他的身边人
I THINK SHE HAS SELF-ESTEEM ISSUES.
我觉得她太不自信
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
呵呵，是哦
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME SHE HAD A BOYFRIEND?
她上次有男朋友是什么时候了
THAT VIRGINIA TECH KID
那个在弗吉尼亚理工大学上学的孩子
WAS JUST TRYING TO PLEASE HIS STRICT KOREAN PARENTS.
就只是为了让他那严厉的韩国父母开心才结婚的
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S DUMB OR SUPER UNATTRACTIVE.
倒不是因为她无趣或者一点都没有魅力
I MEAN, SHE'S PERFECTLY CAPABLE OF BEING NORMAL.
我的意思是，她完全正常
I DON'T WANT HIM TO FIND HIMSELF,
我不希望十年之后
LIKE, TEN YEARS FROM NOW,
他突然发现自己
FAT, BALD, AND IN A LOVELESS MARRIAGE
发福，秃顶，身陷无爱的婚姻
BECAUSE HE WAS RUSHING TO BECOME
只是因为他想曾想努力去成为
THE WORLD'S BEST IRANIAN SON.
这个世界上最好的伊朗儿子而已
THE MEN IN OUR FAMILY DON'T GO BALD.
我们家族的男人没有秃顶基因
OH, I DON'T NEED NEW READING MATERIAL.
哦，我不需要这些新书
I'M ONLY UP TO BOOK TWO OF THE "TWILIGHT" SERIES.
我才看到《暮光之城》的第二本呢
I'M BROADENING YOUR HORIZONS.
我是在开阔你的视野
THIS IS SOME PRETTY SERIOUS STUFF HERE.
这些书里有几本还挺严肃的
I'M ASKING YOU TO READ SOME BOOKS.
我只是想让你多读点书
YOU DON'T NEED TO GET YOUR SEPTUM PIERCED.
又不是让你去穿个鼻环
YET.
至少现在还没有
OH, HEY.
UM, EXCUSE ME,
抱歉
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE BROOKLYN KIDS
这里其实是布鲁克林青少年
MOVIE MAKER CLASS.
电影制作班
I THINK YOU HAVE THE WRONG ROOM.
你们是不是走错教室了
NO, THIS RIGHT.
不，没走错
I'M A MOVIE DIRECTOR.
我是一个导演
SEE YOU AT FIVE.
五点见
AND I'M GONNA POOP.
我要大便
NO! DON'T!
住手
KUJO, COULD YOU PLEASE HOLD--
Kujo，能请你拿着
PUT DOWN THE TRUCK AND HOLD THE CAMERA.
放下那卡车，拿起相机
STOP THROWING.
别再乱扔东西了
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN FIT IT ALL.
我不觉得你能把它装好
HEY, KUJO, THE LENS IS WAY TOO CLOSE TO YOUR BUTT.
啊啊啊啊，Kujo，镜头离你的屁股太近了！
OH, YOU'RE ON OkCupid.
你在看OkCupid（交友网站）啊
MY TAXIDERMIST MET HER HUSBAND ON THAT SITE.
我的标本制作师就是靠那网页找到老公的
I'M JUST LOOKING FOR SOMEONE TO MAKE MY GIRLFRIEND JEALOUS.
我只想找个男人来刺激刺激我女朋友而已
WE'RE ON A BREAK.
我们闹僵了
GOOD LUCK.
祝你好运
FELICIA?
YES?
嗯？
YOU'RE IN A LONG-TERM,
你的恋情
SEEMINGLY HEALTHY RELATIONSHIP.
维持得很好
CAN YOU TELL ME, HOW DO PEOPLE MEET,
你能不能告诉我，人们是怎样做到相遇
AGREE THEY LIKE EACH OTHER,
表白
AND THEN... KEEP ON LIKING EACH OTHER?
并且一直相爱的？
SHARED INTERESTS?
拥有共同的兴趣爱好吧
JACQUES AND I MET AT OCCUPY CHELSEA.
Jacques和我是在切尔西遇到的
I'M GONNA LIE HERE AND TRY TO FORGET
我要躺在这里，努力忘记
WHAT IT FELT LIKE TO BE LOVED.
那种被爱的感觉
COULD YOU PLEASE TURN OFF THE LIGHT?
能请你关一下灯吗
FEEL BETTER.
会好起来的
THANK YOU.
谢谢
HEY.
HI.
YOU WANT A CIGARETTE?
来支烟吗？
I DON'T SMOKE.
我不抽烟
YEAH, ME NEITHER.
我也不抽
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
你在外面干什么？
SOCIAL ANXIETY.
社交恐惧
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
你呢
MORE OR LESS THE SAME.
跟你差不多吧
I'M SHIRIN.
我叫Shirin
MAXINE.
我叫Maxine
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
很高兴认识你
I LOVE DYKES.
我喜欢拉拉
NICE.
很好
I MEAN IT.
真的
YOU KNOW THAT-- THAT WORD IS INCREDIBLY OFFENSIVE.
你知道吗，那个词很冒犯
OH, I'M BISEXUAL,SO IT'S OKAY IF I SAY IT.
我是个双性恋，所以我说那个词没什么关系吧
NO, IT'S STILL OFFENSIVE.
不，依然很冒犯
YOU KNOW HOW I MEANT IT.
你知道我没那个意思
DOESN'T MATTER HOW YOU MEANT IT.
跟你想说什么没什么关系
TOMATO, TO-MAH-TO.
好吧，观点不同咯
WHAT ARE YOU DRINKING?
你在喝什么
I FILLED THIS WATER BOTTLE WITH TEQUILA.
我用矿泉水瓶装了点龙舌兰
CLASSY.
很好
I'M DRINKING WITH A PURPOSE.
我是借酒消愁
YEAH?
嗯？
THIS GUY WITH WHOM I RECENTLY
刚才来的那个男人
HAD AN UNFORTUNATE SEXUAL ENCOUNTER SHOWED UP,
我最近刚和他有过一次很糟糕的性爱
AND NOW I FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
现在我觉得很不舒服
I JUST HATE THE WAY DUDES GET
我就是讨厌
WHEN THEY CAN'T MAINTAIN AN ERECTION.
男人硬不起来的样子
WHAT DO THEY GET LIKE?
他们什么样子？
OH, ARE YOU A GOLD STAR?
天哪你没跟男人做过吗？
NO, I'VE HAD SEX WITH MEN,
我跟男人做过
JUST, UM, NOT THE KIND WHO GO SOFT.
就是，没跟硬不起来的做过
TOUCHÉ.
只靠手活
IT'S THE WORST.
那是最糟糕的
THEY SHUT DOWN,
他们硬不起来
AND THEY GET ALL MOPEY AND OFFENDED
然后你取笑他们的时候
WHEN YOU MAKE JOKES.
他们就变得消沉又粗暴
YEAH, IT'S SO WEIRD THE WAY MEN DON'T ENJOY
是啊太奇葩了，男人居然无法欣赏
HUMOR AT THE EXPENSE OF THEIR PENISES.
那些关于他们鸡巴的幽默
DO YOU WANT SOME?
想来点吗？
SURE.
好
I THINK YOU'RE HOT.
我觉得你很性感
THANKS.
谢谢
I KNOW THAT I DON'T LOOK LIKE I'M INTO GIRLS
我知道我不像拉拉
AND THAT I WAS JUST TALKING ABOUT BEING A BONER KILLER,
然后刚才我还一直在谈论我是多么让人提不起性趣
BUT I AM SUPER SEXY AND SUPER INTO GIRLS.
但我其实超级性感，我也超级爱女人
REALLY?
真的吗
YEAH.
是的
I LIKE GIRLS LIKE YOU.
我喜欢你这样的女孩
LIKE ME?
我这样？
YOU KNOW, LIKE, MANLY,
我是说，有男子气概
BUT ALSO A LITTLE BIT LIKE A LADY.
但同时又有点女性特质
NICE.
很棒
THANK YOU.
谢谢
UM...
ARE YOU HAVING LADY PROBLEMS?
你在为女人困扰吗？
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I'M HAVING LADY PROBLEMS?
为什么你觉得我在为女人烦恼？
BECAUSE IT'S NEW YEAR'S EVE
因为这是跨年夜
AND YOU'RE HEADING OUT BEFORE THE COUNTDOWN.
而你居然在快要倒计时的时候到外面来
MAYBE I'M HEADING OUT
也许我就是出来
TO MEET THE PERSON I'M GONNA KISS AT MIDNIGHT.
找一个我能在午夜亲吻的人
YOU'RE GONNA BE HELLA LATE
那你可有点晚了
'CAUSE IT'S LIKE, TWO MINUTES AWAY.
因为，两分钟之后就是十二点了
WHAT'S HER NAME?
她叫什么名字
LINDA.
SHE SOUNDS LIKE A CUNT.
听起来就像个婊子
WE'RE GOING OUT FOR A COUPLE MONTHS,
我们准备出去几个月
AND WE DECIDED TO MOVE IN TOGETHER.
以及，我们已经确定要同居了
NATURALLY.
理所当然
AND FOUR DAYS AFTER I BREAK MY LEASE
但是当我取消了我的租约
AND SELL EVERYTHING I OWN,
卖掉我所有的东西的四天后
SHE TELLS ME SHE MISSES HER EX,
她居然告诉我她很想念她的前任
AND WHAT THE FUCK AM I SUPPOSED TO DO
在这种情况下
WITH THAT INFORMATION?
我他妈还能做什么？
THAT SUCKS.
太糟了
JUST HAVING TROUBLE DEALING WITH, LIKE, BROOKLYN PARTIES
我就是不能忍受这些布鲁克林派对
AND EVERYONE TALKING ABOUT THEIR KICKSTARTER CAMPAIGNS,
几乎所有人都在谈论他们的集资项目
AND DID YOU SEE THAT GUY WITH THE WAXED DALI MUSTACHE?
你看见那个胡子像打过蜡一样的男人了吗
I MEAN, WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT GUY'S PROBLEM?
我说，这些人是有什么毛病
WHO THE FUCK DOES HE THINK HE IS?
他妈的他以为自己是哪根葱啊
I FIND YOUR ANGER INCREDIBLY SEXY.
我发现你生气的样子超级性感
REALLY?
真的吗
I HATE SO MANY THINGS TOO.
我也讨厌很多东西
WOW.
哇
KEN. HI.
OH! HEY, HI. HOW ARE YOU?
嗨，过得怎么样？
I'M GOOD, THANK YOU.
我很好，谢谢
CARRINGTON, THIS IS SHAYLA.
Carrington，这位是Shayla
I'M SHIRIN. HI.
你好，我其实叫Shirin
OH...
SORRY, MAN. I'M STONED.
对不起，我记错了
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
没事的
WANT A J?
喝点东西？
NO, I'M COOL.THANKS.
不，谢谢
LISTEN, UM...
听着
I'M A TERRIBLE TEACHER.
我不是个好老师
NO.
哪有！
YES, I AM.
真的
UH, THE KIDS HATE ME.
孩子们讨厌我
THEY'RE A GOOD TEN YEARS YOUNGER
他们比我预计的年龄
THAN I THOUGHT THEY'D BE,
小了十岁
AND I CAN'T GET THEM TO LISTEN.
我甚至不能让他们好好听讲
YOU CAN'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY, DUDE.
你不能把原因全归结到自己身上
THEY'RE FIVE.
他们才五岁
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
我都不知道我在干什么
I HAVE THREE KIDS. I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
我有三个小孩，我更不知道我在干什么了
IT'S JUST FAKE IT 'TIL YOU MAKE IT.
反正硬撑着，你会做到的
I'VE LOST CARRINGTON, LIKE, WHAT, FOUR TIMES?
我已经把这家伙弄丢了，大概四次？
RIGHT, BRO?
是吧哥们
JUST DO YOUR BEST, OKAY?
你尽力就好，好吗？
OKAY.
好吧
HEY.
I BELIEVE IN YOU, CHER.
我相信你，Cher
THANK YOU.
谢谢
THEY HAVE NO IDEA YOU'RE BISEXUAL?
他们不知道你是双性恋吗？
I'M SORRY, WHAT COUNTRY IS IT THAT YOU GET STONED TO DEATH
对不起，你知道哪个国家的人被确认为是同性恋之后
IF YOU'RE CONVICTED OF BEING GAY?
会被投石而死吗？
OH, YEAH.
是的
WAIT, I KNOW.
我知道哦
IT'S IRAN,
是伊朗
THE COUNTRY THAT MY ENTIRE FAMILY COMES FROM.
我整个家族可都是从伊朗来的
YOU CAN'T KEEP PLAYING THE PERSIAN CARD
你不能在每次我们争吵的时候
EVERY TIME WE HAVE AN ARGUMENT.
就开始找借口转移话题
YOU NEED TO SEE FOR YOURSELF
你真该亲眼看看
HOW DIFFICULT IT IS TO BE THE CHILD OF IMMIGRANTS.
做一个移民的孩子有多难啊
I WOULD LOVE TO.
我倒真想看看
GREAT.
很好
THEN YOU'RE COMING TO A PERSIAN NEW YEAR PARTY
所以这个星期你会穿着新衣服
THIS WEEKEND IN NEW JERSEY.
出席我们在新泽西州波斯的新年派对吧
AM I COMING AS YOUR DATE?
我以你女友的身份出席吗？
GOD, NO.
天哪，不
YOU'RE DEFINITELY COMING AS MY WHITE FRIEND.
你只是作为我的白人好朋友出席
DO YOU THINK I HAVE A DEATH WISH?
你想让我在那当场判刑吗？
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO WEAR A DRESS.
你知道你得穿裙子吧
NO.
不穿
GOOD. NOW YOU'RE GONNA SEND 'EM?
好了，你们要把这些照片发出去吗
YES.
是的
IT'S LIKE WE JUST STEPPED INTO LIBERACE'S WET DREAM.
这么多女人，哇，好像我在做春梦一样
ISN'T IT SPECTACULAR?
这难道不壮观吗？
YOU KNOW I DON'T LIKE BEING IN ENCLOSED SPACES
你知道我不喜欢封闭空间
WHERE I CAN'T DETECT ANY VISIBLY GAY PEOPLE.
我都不能一眼分辨同志了
WELL, I'M PRETTY SURE UNCLE NEEMA'S HARBORING
我非常肯定那边的Neema叔叔
SOME BI-CURIOUS TENDENCIES.
有双性恋倾向
YOU TALK TO HIM ABOUT IT?
你告诉他了吗
OH, GOD, NO.
天哪没有
PERSIANS COMMUNICATE MOSTLY THROUGH GOSSIP.
我们就八卦八卦而已
SHIRIN?
OH, MY GOD! HI!
天哪，嗨
HI!
MAXINE, THIS IS MITRA,YASSI, MEENU, AND YASSI.
Maxine，这是Mitra、Yassi、Meenu 和Yassi
GUYS, THIS IS MY FRIEND MAXINE.
各位，这是我的朋友Maxine
HEY.
HEY. OH, MY GOD, YOU LOOK AMAZING.
天呐，你看起来美极了
RIGHT. NEXT TO YOU, I LOOK LIKE A BUSBOY FROM CHILI'S.
站在你旁边，我看上去就是一个中东饭馆小工
OH, NO WAY. YOU'RE PRACTICALLY A MODEL.
哪有，你简直跟模特一样
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
是啊是啊
LIKE A "BEFORE" MODEL FOR ACCUTANE.
只不过是像那些过气的模特而已吧
UH, I WOULD KILL FOR YOUR HEIGHT.
要是能有你这个身高，让我干什么我都愿意
AND I WOULD SELL MY FIRSTBORN FOR YOUR SKIN.
要是能有你这皮肤，让我卖掉我的第一胎都行啊
STOP IT.
不会吧
YOU STOP IT.
当然啦
WE NEED TO GET TOGETHER MORE.
我们需要经常聚一聚
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU SINCE YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S FUNERAL.
自从你祖母的葬礼之后我就再没见过你了
HOW'S YOUR FATHER?
你爸爸怎么样
YOU KNOW, HE'S OKAY,
他很好
BUT THEN SOMETIMES HE'LL CRY OUT OF NOWHERE,
但有时候他也会不知道为什么就开始哭起来
AND I'LL BE LIKE,"DAD, WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
然后我就会安慰他说“爸爸你怎么了
YOU'RE EMASCULATING YOURSELF."
这样可不像个男人”
OH, MY GOD! ROYA?
天哪，Roya！
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
发生了什么
YOU WERE IN THE MIDDLE OF A SENTENCE.
你话才说到一半啊
YEAH, EVERY TIME I SEE HER,
每次我看到她
SHE COMPLIMENTS THE WAY I LOOK,
她都会奉承几句我的样子
SHE ASKS ONE PERSONAL QUESTION,
然后问我个私人问题
AND THEN SHE WALKS AWAY WHILE I ANSWER.
当我还在回答的时候，她就找别人交谈去了
AND WHO'S SHE TALKING TO NOW?
她现在在跟谁说话？
THAT'S ROYA.
那是Roya
HER FATHER JUST MADE A LOT OF MONEY IMPORTING SAMOVARS.
她爸爸刚靠进口茶壶赚了很多钱
LET'S GET A DRINK.
去喝一杯吧
WHEN ARE THEY SERVING DINNER?
他们什么时候提供晚餐啊？
MIDNIGHT.
午夜
SERIOUSLY?
真的吗
GOD, YOU KNOW, I SHOULD HAVE TALKED
天呐，我刚才真的应该
ABOUT HER DAD'S COSMETIC DENTAL PRACTICE.
谈谈她爸爸做的那一口假牙气气她
YOU WERE BEING HONEST.
你只是在正经回答问题啊
DO YOU THINK THEY WANT YOU TO BE HONEST AT THESE THINGS?
你认为她们像是希望你在这方面诚实的人吗？
OH, GET A GRIP. YOU'RE A GROWN WOMAN.
别为这个生气了，你已经是成年人了
YOU'VE BEEN TO HOW MANY PARTIES IN YOUR LIFE?
你这一生一共参加了多少派对了？
I DON'T KNOW.A LOT.
我不知道，太多了
AND WHAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
那你知道在派对上
OF HAVING A GOOD TIME AT A PARTY?
什么最重要吗？
DRINKING.
喝酒
AND?
还有呢？
DANCING.
跳舞
AND WHO'S VERY GOOD AT BOTH OF THOSE THINGS?
那谁很擅长这两件事呢？
I AM.
我
THAT'S RIGHT.
这就对了
TWO VODKA TONICS,PLEASE.
两杯伏特加奎宁水，谢谢
THAT WAS AMAZING.
太棒了
I'VE NEVER HAD SO MUCH FUN AROUND PERSIANS BEFORE.
我还是第一次在波斯人堆里这么尽兴
I'M SORRY, I KNOW YOU'RE HAVING A BREAKTHROUGH,
这确实是你的一大突破啊
BUT CAN YOU FIRST EXPLAIN TO ME THIS FIRE THING?
但你能不能先给我解释一下这些火是什么东西
YEAH.
好
SO, THE WEDNESDAY BEFORE NORUZ,
在诺鲁斯节前的那个周三
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO JUMP OVER FIRE
你得从火上面跳过去
TO EXORCISE YOURSELF OF EVIL SPIRITS
来驱散你身上的邪气
AND START THE NEW YEAR FRESH.
并开始新的一年
ONLY WE'RE DOING IT NOW 'CAUSE EVERYONE HAD WORK
但我们这个时候才做这件事，主要是因为每个人都很忙
AND WE'RE HALF-ASSED IRANIANS.
而且我们只能算带点伊朗血统而已吧
GOD, IT'S SUCH A BEAUTIFUL GESTURE.
啊这姿势真带感
UGH, YOU ARE TOTALLY HAVING
你现在就正在体验
ONE OF THOSE "I'M DATING AN IMMIGRANT" MOMENTS.
“和移民约会”的特殊瞬间
LIKE, "ISN'T LEARNING ABOUT OTHER CULTURES
就像 “难道了解其他文化
SO FUN AND ENRICHING? I FEEL LIKE I'M--"
不是一件有趣并且充实的事情吗
你们好，打扰你们了吗
HI.
SO, THIS IS WHERE YOU'VE BEEN?
所以你们一直呆在这里吗
YEAH.
不
WE JUST CAME OUT HERE. WHERE WERE YOU?
我们刚出来，你们刚才在哪？
YOUR FATHER GOT LOST.
你爸爸刚才迷路了
I TOOK THE SCENIC ROUTE.
我只是走了一条美丽的小路而已
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
一点也不好笑
THIS IS MAXINE, MY FRIEND.
这是我的朋友Maxine
MAXINE, MEET MY PARENTS.
Maxine，这是我的父母
HI, MAXINE. OH.
HI.
SO, HOW DO YOU LIKE NORUZ?
你喜欢诺鲁斯节吗
I'M SO SORRY. I THINK I LEFT MY PURSE INSIDE.
对不起，我把钱包落里面了
I GOT TO GO RUN AND GET IT.
我最好去取一下
I WILL SEE YOU REALLY SOON.
马上回来
NICE TO MEET YOU BOTH.
很高兴见到你们
NICE TO MEET YOU.
很高兴认识你
IT SAYS ON YOUR PROFILE THAT YOU'RE AN ARTIST.
档案上说你是一个艺术家
YEAH, I DO A STAND-UP/FOLK MUSIC HYBRID ACT.
是，我在做混合民谣
I HAVE NEVER HEARD OF THAT.
我从没听说过这种风格
YEAH, MY ART DEFIES LABELS.
是的，我的作品独一无二
SOUNDS LIKE IT.
听起来也是
WHY DOES COMEDY ALWAYS HAVE TO
为什么喜剧总是这么mean
BE SO MEAN AND AT SOMEBODY'S EXPENSE?
喜欢在某人的开销上做文章
I WANT TO USE MY COMEDY
我更愿意用我的幽默
TO BRING ATTENTION TO SOCIAL-JUSTICE ISSUES.
把大家的注意力转移到社会公平问题上
YOU'RE VERY PRETTY.
你长得很帅
THANK YOU.
谢谢
WHY DON'T YOU GET TO WORK ON THAT DRINK?
怎么不接着喝呢
CAN I GET A GLASS OF WATER?
我能喝杯水嘛
COME HERE.
过来
CLOSER.
再靠近点
YOU HAVE REALLY NICE HAIR.
你的头发真的很好
THANKS.
谢谢
YOU CAN BE ROUGH WITH ME.
你可以对我粗暴一点
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO.
告诉我你想我做什么
LIE ON THE BED.
躺到床上
OKAY.
好的
FUCK!
靠
COULD YOU PUT THESE ON?
你能穿上衣服吗
WHAT? YOU'RE-- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WANTED WEED.
什么？你才是想抽大麻的那个人
WELL, I REEK OF SEX.
好吧，我讨厌性爱
IT'S GONNA TRIGGER THE DRUG DEALER'S BRAIN
看来只有把那个毒贩子一枪爆头
TO CALL IN HIS RAPIST BRAIN.
才能继续做爱了
YOU'RE LUCKY I VEER MACHO.
你很幸运，我更有男子气概
THANK YOU.
谢谢
YOU'RE AMAZING.
你太棒了
LADIES FIRST.
女士优先
I'M NOT SO GOOD AT SMOKING WEED AROUND PEOPLE.
我不习惯在人前抽大麻
CAN'T HOLD MY THOUGHTS STILL LONG ENOUGH TO THINK THEM.
我无法正常地思考
I HAVE TO CHASE THEM.
我得很努力才能抓住那些想法
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
我懂你的意思
THE OTHER DAY, I HAD A REALLY GOOD IDEA
有一次我在抽大麻的时候
FOR A CHILDREN'S BOOK WHILE I WAS SMOKING WEED,
想出了一个超棒的关于儿童书主题的主意
AND NOW I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IT WAS.
但是现在我已经想不起那是什么了
KEEP SMOKING.YOU'LL GET IT BACK.
那就接着抽，你会想起来的
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN THAT EPISODE OF "SEX AND THE CITY"
你看了那集《欲望都市》吗？
WHERE CARRIE HAS TO PITCH A BOOK FOR CHILDREN
Carrie在给孩子们推销图书的时候
AND SHE PITCHES THIS IDEA
想到了那个
ABOUT A LITTLE GIRL WITH MAGIC CIGARETTES?
魔烟小女孩的点子
AND IT'S REALLY FUNNY.
那很有趣
I HATE "SEX AND THE CITY."
我讨厌《欲望都市》
YEAH, BUT YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
好吧，但你必须承认
IT'S PRETTY FUCKING ENTERTAINING.
这部剧真的很有趣
I THINK IT'S BORING.
我觉得它很无聊
WHO THE FUCK DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
干嘛！你他妈以为自己是谁啊！
OH, MY GOD, ARE YOU INTO "LORD OF THE RINGS"?
天哪 你进入《魔戒》的状态了吗
YOU KNOW, THE OLDER MY DAD GETS,
你知道吗，随着我爸的年纪越来越大
THE MORE HE LOOKS LIKE GOLLUM FROM "LORD OF THE RINGS."
他就越来越像《魔戒》里的咕噜姆
MY DAD, HE'S ALWAYS MAKING THE WORST JOKES,
他总是讲一些无聊的笑话
BUT THEN THIS ONE TIME HE LOST HIS WEDDING RING,
然后有一次，他找不到他的结婚戒指了
AND HE WAS LIKE...
他就像咕噜姆那样
"I NEED MY PRECIOUS."
“我要我的宝贝”
AND WAS LITERALLY THE FUNNIEST THING I'D EVER HEARD.
这真是我听过的最有趣的事情
WHEN I WENT TO SEE THE FILM "PRECIOUS,"
当我去看《珍爱》那部电影的时候
THERE WAS A MENTALLY HANDICAPPED GUY SITTING NEXT TO ME,
坐我旁边的是一个有心理问题的男人
AND HE PUT HIS HAND ON MY LAP DURING THE MOVIE,
他看电影的时候一直把手放在我的膝盖上
AND IT REALLY FREAKED ME OUT.
那是真的吓我一跳
THAT'S HORRIBLE.
可怕
DON'T MAKE FUN OF ME. THIS IS SERIOUS.
别开玩笑，我现在很严肃的
YOU'RE RIGHT, IT'S VERY SERIOUS,
是的，很严肃
AND I CANNOT BELIEVE
我是真的不能相信
THAT LIFETIME HAS NOT MADE THE MOVIE VERSION
这些家伙在看电影的时候对你做的这些事
OF THE TIME SOME DUDE FELT YOU UP AT THE MOVIES.
竟然还没有被拍成电影
YOU'RE SUCH A JERK.
你真是个怪人
YOU LOVE IT.
你就爱我这样的怪人
SHIRIN.
YEAH?
WE'RE THE SAME KIND OF STONED PERSON.
我们都不清醒
THAT IS SO BEAUTIFUL.NO HOMO.
那场景太美了，No Homo
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "NO HOMO"?
"No Homo"什么意思
OH, YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT "NO HOMO" IS?
你居然不知道No Homo是什么
OKAY, SO "NO HOMO" IS THIS THING
No Homo就是
THAT RAPPERS SAY TO EACH OTHER
那些说唱歌手都会这么说
TO, LIKE, NULLIFY THE GAYNESS OF THEIR WORDS.
来显得自己的词没那么gay
THEY COULD BE LIKE,
举个例子
"THOSE ARE SOME REALLY FLY JEANS, MAN. NO HOMO."
你的牛仔裤真棒，真的
OR "YOUR SONG TOUCHED ME. NO HOMO."
你的歌打动我了，真的
LIKE "I LIKE THE WAY YOUR DICK TASTES IN MY MOUTH.
我喜欢你鸡巴的味道
NO HOMO."
EXACTLY.
哈哈，就是这样
I FEEL REALLY LUCKY TO HAVE MET YOU.
遇见你是我的荣幸
NO HOMO?
真的吗？
HOMO.
假的
I LOVE HOW NONE OF YOUR WHITE SHIRTS
我喜欢你白衬衫上
GET THOSE REALLY ANNOYING PIT STAINS
沾上那些烦人的污渍的样子
THAT MINE ALWAYS DO.
就像我的衬衫上也经常会沾上东西一样
I LOVE THAT YOU NOTICED THAT.
我很高兴你能注意到这一点
I HAVE SOMETHING ON MY MIND,
我正在想些东西
BUT IT FEELS TOO SCARY TO SAY OUT LOUD.
但是说出来又太可怕了
SAY IT.
说吧
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING ON YOUR MIND?
你没在想东西吗
MAYBE.
也许
WHAT?
你在想什么
DON'T BE A PUSSY.
别刨根问底
OKAY, LET'S SAY IT AT THE SAME TIME
好，那就数到三
ON THE COUNT OF THREE.
我们一起说
ONE...
TWO...TWO...
I'M FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
我爱上你了
I'M THINKING OF TRANSITIONING INTO A MAN.
我想变性成男人
OF COURSE I'M FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
当然，那是因为我爱上你了
HI, EVERYONE.I'D LIKE TO WELCOME YOU ALL
感谢大家来参加
TO "WITH JUSTICE FOR SOME,"
这个“将公平给予他人”的主题讨论会
WHERE WE LOOK AT THE CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM
我们将讨论关于刑事司法制度
AND ITS BIAS AGAINST THE QUEER COMMUNITY.
和它对同志群体的不公问题
NOW IF ANY OF YOU ARE HERE FOR THE DYKE KNITTING CIRCLE,
如果有在座的是来参加“女同性恋者小组”讨论会的
IT'S BEEN MOVED TO BABELAND ON RIVINGTON.
那个讨论会改了地点，换到了文顿街那边的“宝贝之陆”商店
[注释：Babeland是知名的为女性提供情趣用品、书籍和色情电影的商店]
UM, WE HAVE SOME COPIES OF THE CASE STUDY
我们准备了一些个案的研究文件资料
TO GO AROUND, SO PLEASE TAKE ONE
如果你们手中还没有的话
IF YOU DON'T HAVE IT ALREADY.
请到旁边取一下
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
你来这里干什么
OH, HEY.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO CARES ABOUT GAY RIGHTS.
你又不是唯一一个关心同志权力的人
THIS IS MY EVENT. I MARKED IT ON THE CALENDAR.
这是我的事情，我都把它标记在日历本上了
HEY, GUYS,LET'S HOLD THE SIDE TALK
朋友们，
UNTIL AFTER THE DISCUSSION.
无关的话能留到讨论会结束后再讲吗？
SORRY.
抱歉
WHY DON'T WE START BY INTRODUCING OURSELVES, HMM?
那就从自我介绍开始吧
I AM SASHA, AND I AM A LAW PROFESSOR AT NYU.
我叫Sasha，是纽约大学的法律学教授
HI, I'M MORGAN. I'M AN INTERN AT QUEER AID.
我叫Morgan，是研究艾滋病的医生
MAXINE.
WHAT?
干什么
IS THAT SHIRT NEW?
这件衬衫是新买的吗？
YES.
是的
IT LOOKS REALLY GOOD ON YOU.
你穿着很好看
I'M JOSEPH HENDERSON, AND I'M EXTREMELY
我叫Joseph Henderson，
DISAPPOINTED WITH THE READING MATERIAL YOU'VE PROVIDED.
而且我对你们提供的资料感到非常失望
ABSOLUTELY NO REFERENCE TO CRIME AGAINST NATURE LAWS.
很明显它毫无根据地批判自然法则
IT'S WEIRD SEEING YOU IN SOMETHING I DON'T REMEMBER.
看到你穿着我没见过的衣服，这感觉很奇怪
TRUE, UM, THIS READING DOESN'T REFER TO--
这些材料没有依照
I WAS ARRESTED AT 18 FOR HAVING CONSENSUAL SEX
我18岁的时候曾因为
WITH MY 16-YEAR-OLD BOYFRIEND.
和我16岁的男朋友发生关系而被捕了
I SPENT FOUR YEARS IN JAIL,
我在监狱里蹲了四年
AND AFTERWARDS FORCED TO REGISTER IS A SEX OFFENDER.
还被迫因为性侵犯认罪
WHAT ARE YOU DOING LATER?
你待会要做什么
GOING HOME.
回家
REMEMBER WHEN THAT WAS MY HOME, TOO?
还记得吗，那也曾经是我家
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
别说了
I'M A SEX OFFENDER.
我变成了一个性犯罪者
EVERY TOWN I MOVE TO, EVERY JOB I APPLY FOR--
我每去一个小镇，每申请一份工作都会失败…
MY LIFE IS RUINED.
我的人生彻底毁了
HAVE A DRINK WITH ME LATER?
结束后和我喝一杯吧
NO.
不
I JUST WANT TO TALK.
我只是想和你谈一谈
NO!
不！
...AND I THOUGHT WE WERE GOING TO BE
我想今天我们要
TALKING ABOUT MARGINALIZED WOMEN HERE TODAY.
讨论一下女性被社会边缘化的问题
YES.
好
MY NAME IS SHIRIN.
我叫Shirin
I AM AN IRANIAN BISEXUAL TEACHER,
我是伊朗人，是个双性恋老师
AND I WOULD LIKE TO TAKE YOU OUT FOR A DRINK.
我想请你出去喝一杯
N-- NOW?
现在吗
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
等这个讨论结束后
I WOULD LIKE TO BUY YOU A DRINK.
我就是想请你喝一杯
UM...
EACH FRAME IS A PICTURE.
一个框代表一个分镜
THAT'S WHAT YOU CALL IT, A FRAME.
或者随便怎么说，一个框
AND, UH, WHEN YOU WANT TO HAVE THE CANDY MOVE,
当你想让糖果动起来的时候
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE A PICTURE OF IT WHERE IT IS,
你得拍下它所在的位置
MOVE IT VERY, VERY SLIGHTLY,
一点一点地移动它
AND THEN TO THE NEXT PLACE,
把它移动到下一个分镜头
AND THEN YOU TAKE A PICTURE AND YOU HAVE IT THERE,
你拍照，然后移动
AND THEN MOVE IT A LITTLE BIT--
慢慢地移动
HE TOOK IT!
他吃了！
DO NOT EAT THOSE.
别吃这些！
THOSE ARE FOR THE STOP-MOTION ANIMATION.
这是为定格动画准备的
JUST ONE.
就吃一个
YOU JUST SHOVED LIKE 40 INTO YOUR MOUTH AT ONCE.
你刚才一口气塞了得有40颗
I GET 40, TOO.
我也吃了40颗
ME, TOO!
我也是！
I NEED TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
我想上厕所
ME, TOO!
我也是！
ARE YOU OLD ENOUGH TO GO ON YOUR OWN?
你到了能自己解决的岁数了吗？
I DON'T KNOW.
我不知道
ALL RIGHT, WAIT HERE.
好吧，先在这儿等一下
ALL RIGHT, FIRST SHOT OF THE DAY.
好了，白天的第一场戏
WE HAVE THE FLOCKS OF BIRDS SWARM INTO FRAME,
会有一大群鸟涌入镜头
EVIL-LOOKING RAVENS AND GULLS.
邪恶象征的乌鸦和鸥鸟
HOW'S THAT LOOKING, ART DEPARTMENT?
美术部，怎么样了？
EXCELLENT.
好极了
AND SOUND?
声效部门呢？
IS EVERYTHING SET?
所有都确定了吗？
HI. SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
嗨，对不起打扰了
NOT A PROBLEM.
没关系
WE WERE JUST PREPPING FOR TODAY'S SHOOT.
我们在准备今天的拍摄
GRACIE, WOULD YOU MIND, UH,
Gracie，你能不能
BRIEFING OUR GUEST ON TODAY'S PROJECT?
为她简述一下我们今天的工作？
WE'RE DOING A SHOT-FOR-SHOT REMAKE
我们在重新设计
OF A SCENE FROM "THE BIRDS."
《鸟》的分镜
I'M SHIRIN.I TEACH ACROSS THE HALL.
我叫Shirin，我在走廊对面上课
HI, I'M TIBET. THIS IS THE ADVANCED CLASS.
我叫Tibet，这是提高班
I HAVE A REAL QUICK QUESTION FOR YOU.
我有个问题想问你
YES?
嗯？
SO, YEAH, MY KIDS ARE REAL YOUNG,
我带的小孩都非常小
LIKE FIVE YEARS OLD, AND ONE OF THEM NEEDS
差不多就五岁吧，然后其中有一个
TO USE THE BATHROOM.
想上厕所
YES?
所以呢？
WELL, DO I HAVE TO GO IN WITH HIM, OR IS THAT PERVY?
我需要跟他一起进去吗？会不会有点变态？
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
你没开玩笑吧？
YES.
没啊
JUST STAND BEHIND THE DOOR AND ASK IF HE NEEDS HELP.
就站在门后，问问他是否需要帮助就行啦
OH.
OKAY, THANKS.
谢谢你
NOT A PROBLEM,MY FRIEND.
没关系，朋友
HAVE WE MET BEFORE?
我们之前见过吗
I DON'T THINK SO. I USED TO BE A HAIR MODEL,
没有吧，不过我之前有当过发型模特
SO YOU MIGHT RECOGNIZE ME FROM THAT.
所以你没准曾经在哪见过我照片吧
YEAH, THAT'S PROBABLY IT.
哦，可能是吧
THANK YOU.
谢谢
ALL RIGHT, SECOND SHOT OF THE DAY.
好了，白天的第二幕是
WE HAVE, "SHE IS TRAPPED IN THE PHONE BOOTH
“她被困在电话亭里
AND THE BIRDS ARE FLYING IN TO ATTACK HER."
然后有鸟飞过去啄她”
HAIR AND MAKEUP FOR THAT, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
发型和化妆部，怎么样了？
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING ALL THE WAY OUT TO BROOKLYN.
你们大老远地赶来布鲁克林真是太感谢了
IT IS SO NICE THAT YOU FINALLY GOT TO SEE THE PLACE.
你们最终能看看见到我住的地方，真是太好了
WELL, THE RUG LOOKS QUITE NICE IN HERE.
这块地毯放在这里看上去很不错
THANK YOU.
谢谢
WHY IS THERE ONLY ONE BED?
为什么这里只有一张床？
IT'S EUROPEAN AND THRIFTY.
这是欧洲人的做法，很节省
THERE'S A LOT OF BENEFITS.
有很多很多好处
AND HOW-- HOW'S THAT EUROPEAN?
怎么是欧洲人的做法了？
I HAVE AN ITALIAN FRIEND NAMED CECILIA,
我有一个意大利的朋友叫Cecilia
AND SHE HER BEST FRIEND, UH,
她和她最好的朋友
SHARED ONE BED FOR YEARS,
也是睡同一张床，睡了好几年呢
AND THEY SAVED SO MUCH MONEY ON RENT
她们因此省下了不少钱
THAT THEY WERE ABLE TO AFFORD
以至于她们能够支付起
VERY BIG WEDDINGS TO THEIR BOYFRIENDS.
各自婚礼的费用了
DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND, MAXINE?
Maxine，你有男朋友吗？
NO, I DON'T.
没有
ALSO, IN THE MOVIE "BEACHES,"
还有，电影《海滩》里
THESE TWO BEST FRIENDS SHARED A BED,
那两个好朋友也是睡一张床的
AND IT WAS VERY INEXPENSIVE.
那样很便宜
SO, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
非常感谢你们能来
NICE TO SEE YOU BOTH AGAIN.
很高兴再见到你们
WELL, BYE, GIRLS.
姑娘们，再见
BYE.
再见
LET ME WALK YOU OUT.
我送你们出去
OH, MY GOD.
天哪
YOU...YOU'RE AN ANGEL.
你真是个天使
YOU HAVE TO TELL THEM ABOUT US.
你得把我们的事告诉他们了
I KNOW.
我知道的
YES?
谁啊？
HI.
HEY.
CRYSTAL, DID YOU SEE MY PARENTS?
Crystal，你看到我父母了吗？
OH, YEAH, WE JUST PASSED IN THE HALL.
是的，我们刚刚在过道碰见了
HEY, MAXINE.
HI.
MMM, DON'T MIND HER.
嗯，不用理她
SHE'S UPSET 'CAUSE I'M NOT OUT TO MY PARENTS.
她有点生气，因为我还没向父母出柜
OH, WELL, YOU GUYS LIVE IN A ONE-BEDROOM APARTMENT.
你们睡在一张床上
I'M PRETTY SURE THEY KNOW.
我确信他们已经知道了
DON'T ASK, DON'T TELL.
不问就不说
[注释：DADT是美国军队为回避同性恋这一敏感话题而对同性恋军人所采取的规定，禁止军中谈论这一话题，更不许相关的人员主动公开自己的身份]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
你知道吗
IT'S A PROCESS, AND I'M WORKING ON IT.
这需要一步一步来，而且我已经在努力了
OKAY, WE SHOULD PROBABLY LEAVE.
好了，我们该走了
THINK I'M GONNA BOW OUT.
我想我还是不去了
MAXINE, YOU PROMISED YOU'D GO.
Maxine，你答应过我你会去的
CRYSTAL'S A FRIEND WHO'S GONNA DRESS UP
Crytral的朋友会打扮得像一只农场动物
LIKE A FARM ANIMAL AND TOUCH HERSELF, COME.
然后在那里自慰，跟我们一起去吧
I CAN'T HANDLE AN ART SHOW RIGHT NOW.
我现在不想看艺术展
OKAY.
好吧
I LOVE YOU.
我爱你
BYE.
BYE, MAXINE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR ACCEPTING MY INVITATION.
谢谢你接受了我的邀请
WELL, I COULDN'T HAVE REFUSED EVEN IF I WANTED TO.
啊，即使我想拒绝，在当时那个场合也没办法啊
ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
所有的这些人都还在场
YOU'RE RIGHT.
确实是
I WILL INVITE THEM ALL TO OUR WEDDING.
我会邀请他们都去参加我们的婚礼
UM, WHAT ARE YOU DRINKING?
你在喝什么
IT'S KIND OF LIKE AN OLD FASHIONED.
一款老口味饮料
WANT TO TRY IT?
想试试吗
YEAH.
好
YOU KNOW, I CAN UM, TIE A CHERRY STEM
你知道吗，我可以用我的舌头
INTO A KNOT WITH MY TONGUE.
把樱桃柄打成结
REAL--
真的吗
UM...
嗯
YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD LOOK.
啊，这样看上去不赖
THANK YOU.
谢谢
I FEEL VERY SEXY.
我觉得很性感
I'M SURPRISED BY HOW QUICKLY THEY SPRUNG INTO ACTION.
他们居然这么快就采取行动了
IT'S ALMOST AS IF THEY EXPECTED ME
就像是他们在期待我们
TO MAKE A HUGE MESS.
来制造一场大混乱一样
OH, IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU HAVE A CONSPIRACY ON YOUR HANDS.
听起来像是你已经计划好了一个阴谋一样
YES, I DO.
是的
THIS IS NOT A CASE OF ME BEING A CLUMSY OAF.
我平时可没这么笨拙
I AM A VICTIM OF A LARGER FORCE.
我是一个强压下的受害者
THE BAR AND ALCOHOL INDUSTRY.
酒吧、酿酒业
YES.
是的
OUT TO GET YOU.
都争着要你
YES, 'CAUSE THEY NEED A GIRL LIKE ME TO, YOU KNOW,
是，因为他们正是需要一个像我一样的
HUMILIATE HERSELF, SO THAT THE OTHER PATRONS
可以自黑的女孩，而让其他顾客
CAN FEEL MORE CONFIDENT.
自我感觉更好一点
YEAH, 'CAUSE THEY GET TO GO HOME
这样他们回到家
WITH A DRINK AND A SHOW.
才有闲情喝一杯，再看个节目
YEAH.
是的
OKAY.
好吧
ARE YOU HORRIFIED?
你吓坏了吗？
IS THIS LIKE THE MOST EMBARRASSING THING
这是你见过的
YOU'VE EVER WITNESSED?
最尴尬的事情了吧
I DON'T EMBARRASS EASILY.
我没那么容易就尴尬
I LIKE THAT.
很好
IT'S GETTING LATE.
现在有点晚了
YEAH.
嗯
DO YOU WANT TO SEE MY PLACE?
想去我家看看吗？
I LIVE WITH THIS WOMAN WHO MAY OR MAY NOT
和我一起住的那个女人
BE PRACTICING WITCHCRAFT.
很有可能在练习她的魔法
I'D LOVE TO INTRODUCE YOU.
我很乐意介绍你们认识
CAN I TAKE A RAIN CHECK?
改天行吗？
YEAH, SURE, OF COURSE.
好吧，当然可以
UM... GET THE CHECK, PLEASE?
结账
THIS IS ON ME, LITERALLY AND METAPHORICALLY.
我请客，怎么说都应该是我付钱
NO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
不不，我来吧
NO, I SAID I GOT IT.
我说了我来
I GOT--I GOT THIS ONE.
我来付
THANK YOU.
谢谢
NO, I'VE--LOOK, I GOT IT.
我来付
I SAID I GOT IT.
我说了我来付
I'M NOT TAKING THIS BACK.
我不会把它拿回去的
I INVITED YOU OUT.
是我邀请你的
OKAY.
好吧
WHAT TRAIN YOU TAKING HOME?
你坐哪辆车回家？
ACTUALLY, I'M GONNA STAY AND USE THE BATHROOM.
事实上我还要呆一会，上个厕所
YOU SHOULD JUST GO.
你先走吧
NO, I'LL WAIT.
不，我等你好了
NO, IT'S OKAY. JUST GO.
没事的，你走吧
YOU ARE STUBBORN.
你太固执了
YEAH.
是的
THANKS FOR COMING OUT WITH ME.
谢谢你同意和我出来
WELL, THANK YOU FOR ASKING ME.
谢谢你邀请我
OKAY, BYE.
再见
BYE.
HI.
UM, CAN I HAVE THE CHEAPEST RED YOU'VE GOT?
请给我一杯你们这儿最便宜的红酒
THANK YOU.
谢谢
CAN I ASK WHAT YOU'RE HAVING?
我能问问你在喝什么吗
THE CHEAPEST RED THEY HAD.
这里最便宜的红酒
HOW IS IT?
尝起来如何
ALCOHOLIC.
酒精味
WITH AN OAKY FINISH.
余味还不错
SOUNDS GOOD.
听起来不错
SORRY, I'M NOT WELL-VERSED IN WINE TALK.
抱歉，我对酒的话题并不精通
"OAKY FINISH" WAS A NICE TOUCH.
“余味不错”就是一个很好的描述了
THANKS.
谢谢
I'M TED.
我叫Ted
SHIRIN.
SHIRIN. HI.
HI.
UM, DO YOU LIVE AROUND HERE?
你住在这附近吗？
HI.
OH, HEY, WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
嗨，这是你的朋友吗？
THIS IS SHIRIN.
这是Shirin
SHIRIN, I'M MARIE.
我叫Marie
HI.
YEAH, WE UH, LIVE A FEW BLOCKS FROM HERE, ACTUALLY.
其实我们住的地方离这里只有几个街区
MM-HM.
COOL.
HEY, DO YOU WANT TO COME SIT WITH US?
所以你想来坐坐吗？
OKAY.
可
I'M LIKE ONE BAD ROMANTIC ENCOUNTER AWAY
自从搬到法国换了我的身份证之后
FROM MOVING TO FRANCE AND CHANGING MY IDENTITY.
我就与浪漫越来越远
HMM.
DO YOU WANT AN OLIVE?
想来一粒橄榄吗？
NO, I'M OKAY.
不用了
BUT MAYBE I SHOULD GO TO, LIKE,
也许我应该去
A LESS GLAMOROUS PLACE, LIKE SLOVENIA OR SOMETHING,
魅力值没那么高的地方，像是斯洛文尼亚
WHERE MY CHANCES OF POPULARITY WOULD BE GREATER.
这样我的人气值会高一些
HMM.
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
它们真的很好吃
I'M OKAY.
不用了，谢谢
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME WINE?
还想来点酒吗？
YEAH.
好
WHY ARE YOU GIGGLING?
你为什么在笑？
I'M JUST--I'VE BEEN PLOTTING ON HOW
我只是在想
TO GET YOU EAT ONE OF THESE OLIVES,
如何才能让你吃一颗橄榄
BECAUSE THEY'RE COVERED IN GARLIC,
因为他们裹着一层蒜
AND WE'VE ALREADY HAD SOME.
我们已经吃过了
OH.
I GUESS IT'S SORT OF AN ALL OR NOTHING KIND OF THING.
这只是个吃或者不吃的问题而已吧
PROBLEM SOLVED.
现在问题解决了
YOU SHOULD SHOW HER YOUR LATEX OUTFIT.
你应该展示一下你的那身橡胶装
YOU HAVE A LATEX OUTFIT?
你有橡胶装？
YEAH. YEAH, I HAVE TO OIL UP TO PUT IT ON.
有啊，不过我得先涂层油再穿上
YEAH, PLEASE PUT THAT ON.
哦，你一定要穿上让我看看
OH.
THANKS.
谢谢
DRINK?
来一杯吗
YEAH.
可
UM, SO IN WHAT SITUATION DOES A PERSON FIND THEMSELVES
所以，在什么场合人们会觉得
IN NEED OF LATEX OUTFIT?
自己需要穿这种橡胶装？
BURLESQUE SHOWS, PLAY PARTIES,
滑稽表演、派对
ALL KINDS OF PLACES, REALLY.
其实任何地方都可以，真的
AH.
UM, OKAY, BUT-- BUT HERE'S MY QUESTION.
好吧，不过我还有个问题
WHY DO THE WOMEN HAVE TO DRESS UP
为什么女人就得
LIKE SLUTTY CUPCAKES?
穿成这么色情的样子
WHAT ABOUT THE DUDES?
男人为什么就不用这么穿？
WELL, I HAVE A LATEX OUTFIT, TOO.
嗯，其实我也有一身橡胶装
THAT'S SOUNDS HORRIBLE.
可怕
OH, IT'S REALLY CUTE.
不不不，那很可爱的
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE YOUR WORD ON THAT ONE.
我会记住你的话的
THANKS.
谢谢
CHEERS.
干杯
ARE YOU OKAY?
你还好吗
YEAH.
嗯
I'M SORRY, I-- I JUST GOT A LITTLE IN MY HEAD
对不起，我就是想了点别的事情
FOR A MINUTE.
不过只想了一小会
NO, IT'S-- IT'S OKAY.
没事的
IT'S OKAY.
SO THIS IS MY FIRST TIME DOING THIS.
这是我的第一次3P
WELL, WE CAN TAKE IT SLOW.
我们可以慢慢来的
THANK YOU.
谢谢
I LIKE YOU.
我喜欢你
A LOT.
很喜欢
THANK YOU.I LIKE YOU, TOO.
谢谢,我也很喜欢你
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE DON'T HAVE TO FUCK.
你知道吗，我们不一定非得做爱的
YOU KNOW, WE CAN JUST HANG OUT,
我们可以就一起随便逛逛
PLAY MONOPOLY OR SOMETHING.
玩玩大富翁，或者干点别的
THAT ACTUALLY SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF FUN.
听起来很有趣
GREAT.I HAVE THE CLUE VERSION.
我还有大富翁的谜题特别版呢
OH.
YEAH.
THAT'S REALLY COOL.
很棒
YEAH.
IT'S AWESOME.
很酷
HONEY.
亲爱的
YOU TWO CAN STAY AS YOU ARE.
你们两个就随意吧
UM, I SHOULD GET DRESSED.
我还是穿上衣服吧
NO, DON'T.
哦，别
IT'S OKAY.
没事的
UM, I SH-- I SHOULD GO.
我该走了
NO, NO.
别走
TED, TED,TELL HER TO STAY.
Ted，告诉她让她留下来
THANKS.
谢谢
I REALLY DON'T WANT THIS TO BE THE LAST TIME
我真的不希望这次
THAT WE SEE EACH OTHER.
是我们的最后一次见面
ME, NEITHER.
我也不希望
HOW COME NO ONE SAID YOU HAD TO COME DRESSED
怎么会没人告诉你，你应该像《小淘气》中
AS ONE OF YOUR FAVORITE CHARACTERS FROM "THE LITTLE RASCALS"?
你最喜欢的角色那样打扮
THAT'S THE GREAT THING ABOUT PRIDE.
这可是关乎自尊呢
PEOPLE HERE LOOK LIKE THEY DIDN'T GO TO COLLEGE.
这里的人看起来都像没上过大学一样
YOUR ATTITUDE IS REALLY PISSING ME OFF.
我不喜欢你的态度
SORRY.
对不起
DID YOU SEE THE DRAG QUEEN? THAT'S MY FRIEND.
你看那边的变装皇后，他是我的朋友
HOW COME THE ONLY ASPECT OF GAY CULTURE
为什么你唯一能接受的gay文化
THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU IS DRAG?
就只有变装呢？
HEY, WHAT AM I GOOD AT?
你知道我擅长什么吗？
I DON'T KNOW, WHAT?
我不知道，是什么？
DRINKING AND DANCING, REMEMBER?
喝酒和跳舞啊，记得吗
LET'S HAVE FUN.
我们来玩吧
FINE.
好
KISS ME.
吻我
TWO VODKA RED BULLS,PLEASE.
两杯伏特加加红牛，谢谢
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
AAH.
CAN I GET ANOTHER ONE?
我能再来一杯吗？
YOU HAVIN' FUN?
你尽兴了吗？
SURE.
当然
LOOK, BEFORE YOU ASK, NO, I'M NOT AN F TO M TRANSSEXUAL.
我话说在前面，我不是男转女的变性人
UH, SORRY TO DISAPPOINT.
不好意思啊，让你失望了
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
你在这里做什么?
MY SISTER AND I MADE A BET.
我和我妹妹打了个赌
I'M GUESSING SHE WON?
我猜她赢了吧
AH... CORRECT.
呃，是的
I'M MAXINE.
我叫Maxine
GEORGE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
很高兴认识你
I CAN SEE YOU.
你别以为我看不到你在做什么
SHIRIN, STOP.
Shirin，听我说
FUCK YOU.
滚开
I'M SORRY.I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
对不起，我自己都不清楚刚刚发生了什么
WHAT THE FUCK? HE'S A MAN.
什么？他可是个男人！
IT WAS LIKE KISSING A BABY.
就像吻小孩一样
WHAT?
什么？
IT'S JUST LIKE LIPS TOUCHING.
就只是碰碰嘴唇而已，不带感情
I HATE YOU SO MUCH WHEN YOU'RE DRINKING.
我太讨厌你喝酒了
I'M SO--
我很
DO NOT TOUCH ME.
别碰我！
ARE YOU OKAY?
你还好吗？
YOU SHOVED ME OFF, LIKE, REALLY VIOLENTLY.
你居然这么暴力地推我
YOU CHEATED ON ME.
是你先背叛我的
YOU HIT ME.
但是你打我！
I FEEL SICK.
我很难过
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
别哭
DON'T.
I'M SORRY.YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE ME.
对不起，请原谅我
WHO IS HE?
他是谁？
JUST SOME GUY AT THE BAR.WE WERE JUST DRINKING.
就是一个刚认识的男人，我们只是一起喝酒
AND YOU WERE LIKE,"WANT TO KISS A LESBIAN?"
但你表现得就像是“想试试亲亲蕾丝吗”
IT ONLY LASTED A SECOND.
可是那只是很短时间的事情啊
I WAS WATCHING YOU. IT WAS FOREVER.
我看了你很久，你们就像是要吻到天荒地老一样
HEY. I AM SORRY.
我错了
YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE ME.
你得原谅我
WHO SPENDS $300 ON A GARTER BELT?
卧槽，谁会在吊袜带上花300刀啊！
MAY I HELP YOU?
有什么我可以帮您的吗？
UH, WE'RE JUST LOOKING.
我们只是看看
ACTUALLY, YES.
好吧
UM, I'M LOOKING FOR THE GROWN-UP UNDERWEAR
我想要成人内裤
OF A WOMAN IN CHARGE OF HER SEXUALITY
要一款专门为那些性感并且勇于尝试的
AND NOT AFRAID OF CHANGE.
女士设计的
I'VE GOT THAT.
我懂了
THIS JUST CAME IN FROM FRANCE.
这是刚从法国到的货
IT'S A BIT PINK.
有点小粉红啊
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU TRY IT ON FOR YOURSELF?
你可以试穿一下
LET ME KNOW WHAT YOU NEED,
然后让我知道你需要什么
AND I'LL GET A ROOM READY FOR YOU.
我会为你准备一个试衣间
I ACTUALLY NEED TO STOCK UP ON PANTIES.
其实我只需要买一些内裤而已
MY EX-GIRLFRIEND UH, CUT UP MOST OF MINE,
我的前女友几乎把我的内裤全剪了
SO I'M GONNA NEED MORE.
所以我要买一些
WHAT ABOUT BRAS?
你需要胸罩吗？
I DON'T WEAR THOSE.
我不穿那个
WHY NOT?
为什么不
JUST DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH TO WORK WITH,
没什么必要穿
SO IT FEELS A LITTLE SILLY.
而且胸罩有点蠢
YOU KNOW, LIKE WHEN LITTLE GIRLS CARRY PURSES.
就像小女孩都用起了手提包一样
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
你叫什么名字
SHIRIN.
YOU ARE A WOMAN, AND YOU HAVE BREASTS,
你是一个女人，你有胸
AND THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH THEM.
所以没什么错啊
YEAH, I KNOW.
我知道
YOU DESERVE A SEXY, SUPPORTIVE BRA,
你需要一款性感的、有支撑作用的内衣
JUST LIKE ANY OTHER WOMAN.
就像其他女人一样
OKAY.
好吧
YOU WERE WITH A WOMAN FOR HOW LONG,
你跟你的前女友在一起有多久？
AND SHE DIDN'T HELP YOU FIND THE RIGHT BRA?
她居然没有帮你寻找到一款适合你的内衣
A WHILE.
一段时间吧
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR EX-- WHAT'S HER NAME?
我觉得你前女友…她叫什么名字？
MAXINE.
她叫Maxine
SOUNDS LIKE MAXINE WAS DESTRUCTIVE TO YOUR PANTIES
听起来，Maxine不仅摧毁了你的内裤
AND YOUR SELF-ESTEEM.
还摧毁了你的自信
I'M SO SORRY.
不好意思
IS THIS REALLY NECESSARY?
这真的有必要吗？
I'M FINE.I JU-- I JUST NEED UNDERWEAR.
没关系，反正我只是需要内裤而已
JUST BECAUSE YOUR BREASTS ARE SMALL
你的胸很小
DOESN'T MEAN THEY'RE NOT LEGITIMATE.
并不意味着它们有错
I KNOW.
我懂
IT'S OKAY TO BE ANGRY.
你有理由生气
OH, MY GOD.
天哪
LET'S TRY THAT ON.
先试试这个
YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE I DIDN'T THINK I DESERVED A BRA,
我认为我不需要内衣是因为
BECAUSE I DON'T SEE MYSELF AS A REAL WOMAN.
我并没有把自己当做真正的女人看待
IT'S ABOUT MORE THAN JUST FABRIC.
内衣不只是一块布
YEAH, AND I'VE BEEN WEARING BIKINI BOTTOMS FOR MONTHS.
有一段时间我一直穿比基尼当内裤
WELL, THAT'S BASICALLY INVITING PEOPLE
好吧，这么做所吸引的人
WHO DON'T RESPECT YOU INTO YOUR BEDROOM.
只不过是想爬上床和你做而已
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I DID, AND NOW I'M LIKE SEEING HER
我经常那么做，而且我就要在周六的派对上
AT A PARTY ON SATURDAY,
见到她了
AND HOW DO I EXPECT ANYONE TO TAKE ME SERIOUSLY
如果我不穿内衣
IF I AM NOT WEARING A BRA?
我怎么能希望别人来认真对待我呢
I TAKE YOU SERIOUSLY.
我很认真对待你啊
THAT DOESN'T COUNT.
你不算
STUNNING.
很迷人
GOD, I HATE YOUR FRIENDS.
天哪，我讨厌你的朋友
MY FRIENDS ARE MY FAMILY.
我的朋友就像我的家人
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT'S LIKE,
你根本不知道那是什么感受
TO HAVE TO CHOOSE YOUR OWN FAMILY BECAUSE THE ONE YOU WERE BORN INTO--
你不能选择你出生在什么家庭
OH, COME ON, ENOUGH OF THIS LESBIAN ORPHAN PROPAGANDA.
哦省省吧，别再说这种女同孤儿院一样的东西了
YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL BORN INTO SHIT FAMILIES.
我们都出生在糟糕的家庭
WE DEAL WITH IT.
我们都需要解决这个问题
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
你有什么毛病
MY PROBLEM IS I HAVEN'T BEEN FUCKED IN LIKE THREE WEEKS.
我的问题就是我已经快三个礼拜没做爱了
I AM NOT GONNA TALK ABOUT THIS ON MY BIRTHDAY.
我不想在我生日的时候讨论这问题
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY? WHAT ARE YOU, EIGHT?
在你的生日这天？你当你几岁了，八岁小孩吗
SO YOU HAPPENED TO BE BORN. BIG FUCKING DEAL.
你碰巧出生在这一天，这天还他妈成大日子了
OH, I'M SORRY, ALL ATTENTION MUST REVOLVE AROUND YOU
哦对不起，我都忘记了，你必须得到每个人关注的焦点才罢休
100% OF THE TIME. I FORGOT.
每时每刻都是
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE. I'M NOT LIKE THAT.
错，我才不是这样的
I DON'T KNOW WHY I GET SO SHOCKED WHEN YOU DO SHIT LIKE THIS.
我都不知道为什么你这样做的时候，我会这么震惊
YOU'RE A GROWN WOMAN IN A CREEPY,
你就是一个依赖父母的
CO-DEPENDENT RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR PARENTS.
奇怪的女人而已
IT'S TOTALLY NORMAL, AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA
这很正常好吗，而且你根本就不懂这些
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT BECAUSE YOU COMPLETELY ABANDONED YOUR FAMILY.
因为你完完全全地切断了与家庭的联系
IT WASN'T A CHOICE!
我又没得选！
OF COURSE, IT'S A CHOICE!
你当然有得选了
SAYS THE CLOSET CASE!
那你就把你的秘密说出来啊！
THEY KNOW I KNOW THEY KNOW.
他们其实知道我已经知道他们意识到我是同性恋这事了
I'M WAITING FOR THE RIGHT TIME TO BRING IT UP,
只是出于对他们的尊敬
OUT OF RESPECT FOR THEM.
我在找一个合适的机会告诉他们
I THINK YOU AND I SEE THE WORLD TOTALLY DIFFERENTLY.
我认为我们的世界观完全不同
WE DO. YOU KNOW, YOU THINK THAT I'M A BAD PERSON
的确很不一样，就因为我没像你想的那样出柜
BECAUSE I'M NOT COMING OUT ON YOUR TERMS,
你觉得我就是个坏人
AND I DON'T AGREE WITH THAT.
不过我自己可没这么想
THAT IS NOT TRUE. I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
才不是这样，我没那么说过
THAT'S TOTALLY TRUE. YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME.
明明就是这样，你根本不听我在说什么
I'M LISTENING TO YOU, AND EVERYTHING YOU'RE SAYING
我听着呢，但是你说的每句话都是错的
IS PISSING ME OFF AND COMPLETELY INACCURATE.
都让我觉得无比讨厌
YOU ARE RUINING MY BIRTHDAY.
你毁了我的生日
YOU'RE RUINING MY TWENTIES.
你毁了我的20岁
I CAN'T--
我不能
I DON'T HAVE THE PATIENCE TO DEAL WITH YOU.
我没耐心再跟你耗下去了
THAT'S FINE.LET'S BREAK UP.
行啊，那就分手吧
FINE.
分就分
OKAY
好
IF YOU'RE GONNA GO, JUST GO. YOU DON'T GET TO TAKE THINGS.
如果你想走就走吧，有本事别拿东西
I GOT YOU THOSE PANTIES.
这些内裤还是我帮你买的
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
才不是
FUCK YOU.
你麻痹
WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU?
你他妈到底有什么毛病
I GOT THESE FOR YOU.
这是事给你买的
YOU'RE A FUCKING CRAZY PERSON!
你个疯子
YOU WANT TO PLAY LIKE THIS?
你真的想这么玩吗？
DO YOU WANT TO DO THIS? OKAY.
你非得这么搞嘛？好啊！
I BOUGHT ALL THE BOOZE FOR THIS PARTY.
这些酒都是我买的
ARE YOU HAPPY? IS THIS WHAT YOU WANTED?
你开心了吗？这就是你想要的吗？
YOU KNOW WHAT-- DON'T BOTHER TELLING YOUR PARENTS ABOUT US.
你知道吗，你再也不用费心怎么把我们的事告诉你父母了
I KNOW YOU, AND THE MORE THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
我很了解你，我越来越觉得
THIS IS PROBABLY JUST A PHASE.
这可能只是阶段性的而已
GOD, THIS WAS SUCH A WASTE.
天啊，我浪费在你身上太多时间了
HEY.
HI.
NICE HAIR.
发型不错
THANKS.
谢谢
THIS IS JON FRANCIS.
这是Jon Francis
THIS IS MAXINE.
这是Maxine
JON, SHOW HER YOUR CHEST TATTOO.
Jon，给她秀一下你胸上的纹身
IT TOOK THEM FOUR HOURS TO DO IT.
花了四个小时去纹
IT'S A GIANT SQUID BITING A SPERM WHALE.
这图案是只大乌贼打抹香鲸
COOL.
酷哦
HOW ARE YOU?
过得怎么样
I'M OKAY. YOU?
我很好，你呢？
GOOD.
挺好的
YOU SHOULD MEET MY DATE.
你该见见我的女朋友
WHERE IS SHE?
她在哪
AT THE BAR, GETTING US DRINKS.
就在吧台，正在拿喝的
GREAT. SHE SOUNDS AWESOME.
好啊，听起来还可以
SHE IS.
她确实很棒
GOD, LOOK HOW THINGS WORKED OUT FOR BOTH OF US.
你看看我们现在
YOU HAVE YOUR LADY WHO FETCHES YOU DRINKS AT A BAR,
你有了一个像女仆一样帮你拿饮料的女友
LIKE A MAID, AND I HAVE MY HUNKY REBEL WITH A CAUSE.
机缘巧合我也有了一个性感强壮的男友
OH, WHAT'S THE CAUSE?
什么机缘巧合？
JON'S SPEARHEADING A CAMPAIGN TO BRIDGE THE GAPS
Jon是促进布鲁克林贵族的
OF GENTRIFICATION IN BROOKLYN THROUGH MASS KOMBUCHA BREWING.
大规模康普茶酿造的生产活动领头人
THAT'S NOT A THING.
那算什么机缘巧合
YEAH, WE'RE GONNA GO DANCE NOW.
现在我们要去跳舞了
JON'S KNOWN ALL OVER BUSHWICK FOR HIS VOGUEING.
Jon跳舞在布什维克可有名了
[注释：布什维克为布鲁克林北部的社区]
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.T's AN AMAZING DANCER.
好巧啊，T跳舞也很棒
OH, IS SHE?
是吗
YEAH.
是的
SHE GOES TO HER WEST AFRICAN DANCE CLASS RELIGIOUSLY.
她定期去上非洲舞课
IS SHE BLACK?
她是黑人？
NO.
不
SHE SOUNDS AWESOME.
她听起来很不错
SHE IS.
是的
TIBET?
HEY, SHIRIN.
THIS IS YOUR DATE?
她就是你的约会对象？
YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
你们两个之前就认识？
YEAH, WE WORK TOGETHER.
是，我们一起工作
TIBET,THIS IS JON FRANCIS.
Tibet，这位是Jon francis
JON, SHOW HER YOUR CHEST TATTOO.
Jon，给她秀一下你胸上的纹身
UH, TIBET'S A FORMER HAIR MODEL.
Tibet曾经是一个发型模特
YEAH, I HEARD.
是啊，我知道
MAXINE AND I USED TO DATE.CAN YOU IMAGINE?
你能想象吗，Maxine和我曾经是一对
NOPE.
不能
WHY NOT?
为什么不能？
I THOUGHT YOU WERE STRAIGHT.
我以为你是直的
FUCK YOU.
你滚
WHOA, THAT IS UNCALLED FOR!
喂，你有必要吗
YOUR HAIR IS UNCALLED FOR.
你的头发也没必要
BABY, LET'S GO GET HIGH.
亲爱的我们去high吧
I DON'T WANT TO GET HIGH.
我不想去
WHATEVER.
随你吧
WHAT IS UP WITH YOUR PASSIVE DISINTEREST IN EVERYTHING?
你怎么对什么东西都没兴趣
SERIOUSLY, WHAT HAPPENED AT WESLEYAN
说真的， 在卫斯理教会里到底发生了什么
THAT DID THIS TO YOU?
导致你变成现在这个样子
MAXINE, MAYBE WE SHOULD GO.
Maxine，我们走吧
OH, SHUT UP, TIBET.
闭嘴，Tibet
NO ONE CARES WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY.
没人在意你说了什么
YOU HAVE THE SEX APPEAL OF A FERRET.
你一点都不性感，就跟只雪貂一样
I'M IN HERE.
里面有人
IT'S MAXINE.
我是Maxine
GO AWAY.
走开
THE DOOR WAS UNLOCKED.
门没锁
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU COULD TRY TO REPLACE ME
你居然用这么一个白痴
WITH THAT FETUS.
来取代我的位置
I'M NOT TRYING TO REPLACE YOU.
我没想过用别人取代你
I HATE JON.
我讨厌Jon
I KNOW.
我知道
TAKE A CAB HOME.
打的回家
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
你会好起来的
ALL RIGHT, OKAY,
好吧
EVERYBODY PLEASE COME SIT. I HAVE A FILM.
所有人都坐下，我有一部电影
EVERYBODY STOP PLAYING
所有人都别玩了
AND COME WATCH THE MOVIE.
都过来看电影
ALRIGHT, SO THIS IS ONE OF THE FIRST FILMS
好了，这是一部早期电影
THAT WAS EVER MADE FOR AUDI--
这是用来……
IT'S NOT APPROPRIATE FOR OUR AGE.
这个不适合我们这个年纪看
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BE LIKE THAT?
你干嘛这么做
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
你们在看什么
KUJO, GROUCHO, WHY ARE YOU NOT SITTING HERE?
Kujo、Groucho，你们怎么不坐过来
I'M SCREENING A FILM.
我在放电影呢
WE'RE WATCHING A MOVIE.
我们在看电影
YES! NO, I WANT YOU RIGHT HERE.
好吧，你们统统给我过来
WHAT HAPPENED?
怎么了
OKAY...
没事
DO WE GOTTA CLEAN ALL THAT UP?
我们把它清理干净吧
THERE'S TOO MUCH.
太多了
HEY, GUYS. LEAVE IT.
孩子们，别干了
JUST LEAVE IT.
不用干了
NEW PLAN.
新计划
I SAY FORGET THE STOP MOTION.
我们放弃之前的那个方案
WHAT MOVIE DO YOU GUYS WANT TO MAKE?
你们想拍什么东西？
I WANT TO MAKE A MOVIE ABOUT FARTS.
我要拍一个放屁的电影
ALRIGHT, GREAT. LET'S DO IT.
好极了，就做这个
FARTS.
放屁
ZOMBIES!
僵尸
ZOMBIES? AWESOME.
僵尸？很好
BOOGERS!
鼻屎！
WHAT ELSE HAVE WE GOT? IT'S A GOOD START.
这是一个很好的开始，我们还要什么元素呢？
WHAT ELSE DO WE HAVE HERE?
我们还要什么？
I WANT BOOGERS IN MY MOVIE.
我想要鼻屎
BOOGERS.THERE WE GO.
鼻屎，好的
BUTTS.
屁股
YOU GUYS ARE IN THE ZONE. KEEP IT FLOWING.
你们很棒，继续想
NAKED NINJAS!
裸体武士！
I'M NOT A ZOMBIE.I'M JUST A BOY.
我不是僵尸，我是个小男孩
BUT YOU'RE MAKING THE ZOMBIE MASK.
我们只是做个僵尸的面具而已
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF IT'S YOUR CHARACTER.
就算你的角色是僵尸也没有关系
YOU'RE JUST MAKING IT UP.
你只是化妆成僵尸而已
CAN IT HAVE MORE EYES THAN TWO?
我可以在面具上多弄几只眼睛吗？
YES.
当然了
ZOMBIES HAVE AS MANY EYES
你们想要几只眼睛
AS YOU WANT THEM TO HAVE.
僵尸就能有几只眼睛
WELCOME TO THE "BROOKLYN KIDZ MOOVIE MAKER,
欢迎来到“布鲁克林小孩电影制作班的
FINAL SCREENING."
最终放映会”
FIRST WE SCREEN THE ADVANCED CLASS,
我们先放映的是提高班的成片
AND THE NON-ADVANCED CLASS.
然后放映初级班制作的片子
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
再次感谢你们的到来
I WROTE THAT SPEECH.
那讲稿是我写的
I LOVE FARTING.
我喜欢放屁
I CAN'T FART.
但是我不能
OH, YOU GUYS.
啊，谢谢你们
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL.THANK YOU SO MUCH.
花太美了，谢谢你们
YOU'RE WELCOME.
不客气
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST.
你们是最棒的
THANK YOU.
谢谢
SHIRIN.
HI, KEN.
SO, THAT WAS...
那片子很
DISGUSTING. I'M SO SORRY.
很恶心，我很抱歉
ACTUALLY, I THOUGHT IT WAS HILARIOUS.
事实上，我觉得很有趣
SERIOUSLY?
真的吗？
YEAH. I WAS CRACKIN' UP.
是的，很好笑
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR SAYING THAT.
谢谢你这么说
LET'S FACE IT, FARTS ARE FUNNY.
放屁真的很有趣
I AGREE. FARTS ARE FUNNY.
我同意，确实很有趣
THANK YOU.
谢谢
HAVE YOU SEEN CARRINGTON?
你看见Carrington了吗？
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
嘿，你在那里干什么
HIDING.
躲着
I'M SORRY I'VE BEEN SUCH A DICK ABOUT LAYLI.
很抱歉我之前对Layli的态度太差了
AW, COME ON, FORGET IT.
没事的，别放在心上
COME ON, LET'S GO INSIDE.
好了，我们进屋吧
MY OLD ROOMMATE MAXINE AND I WERE IN A RELATIONSHIP.
我的前室友和我曾经在一起过
AH, SO YOU'RE A LESBIAN.
啊，所以你是拉拉
I WAS PRETTY INTO ALL THE GUYS I WAS WITH,
我和男人相处的也不错
SO I THINK I'M BISEXUAL.
我想我是双性恋吧
AND THAT'S A THING?
这很重要吗
I'M AFRAID SO.
恐怕是的
ALL RIGHT.
好吧
HOW DO YOU THINK MOM AND DAD ARE GONNA TAKE IT?
你说爸妈会不会接受这个？
OH, YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL THEM NOW THAT IT'S OVER.
既然都结束了，何必要告诉他们
SEEMS LIKE A PRETTY BIG THING TO NOT BE HONEST ABOUT.
欺骗总是不对的
FINE.
好吧
JUST UH, WAIT UNTIL AFTER THE WEDDING, ALRIGHT?
还是等到婚礼结束后再说吧
YOU ARE SUCH A DICK.
你太混蛋了
WELL, AT LEAST I'M NOT A SEXUALLY CONFUSED NARCISSIST.
至少我不是一个性向模糊的自恋狂
CAN WE PLEASE GO INSIDE?
我们能进去了吗？
HEY, CAN I BE YOUR BEST MAN?
我能当你的伴郎吗？
NO, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
绝不
I ATE BEFORE I CAME.
我来之前吃过了
OW, FUCK!
妈的
OW! SHIT.
靠
I'M SORRY I RUINED YOUR SCARF.
很抱歉我毁了你的围巾
没关系
MOM, I'M A LITTLE BIT GAY.
妈妈，我有点同性恋倾向
不，你才不是
YES, I AM.
是的，我就是
AND I WAS IN LOVE WITH MAXINE.
我和Maxine恋爱过
SHH.
嘘
SHIRIN, ARE YOU OKAY?
Shirin，你还好吧
I'M OKAY.
我很好啊
STOP BREATHING SO LOUD.
你呼吸得太大声了
OKAY.
好吧
HAS YOUR MOM MENTIONED IT?
你妈妈提起那件事了吗？
NO.
没
MAYBE SHE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU MEANT.
也许她没懂你的意思吧
NO, SHE KNOWS FOR SUREWHAT'S UP.
不，她完全知道怎么回事
I'M GONNA BRING IT UP IN ABOUT A MONTH.
这段时间我会再跟她提一提
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
我真为你感到骄傲
THANKS.
谢谢
THERE'S A PARTY AT THE LOFT ON SATURDAY.
周六在阁楼上会有个派对
YOU SHOULD BRING THAT WAITER, BRENDAN.
你可以带上那个叫Brendan的服务员
UM, I WOULD, BUT I KINDA WANT TO SEE IF JACQUES
嗯，但是我还是想看看
AND FELICIA TRY TO SEDUCE ME.
Jacques和Felicia会不会来色诱我
IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
绝不可能
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU THINK THEY'RE SWINGERS.
我不知道为什么你会觉得他们是会搞3P的人
I JUST GET THAT VIBE.
我就是有那种感觉
YOU SHOULD INVITE THAT GAY LAWYER.
你应该邀请那个同志律师
DID YOU GUYS TOUCH TONGUES?
你们舌吻了吗？
NO, WE DIDN'T,
没有
AND IT ACTUALLY HURT MY FEELINGS.
问这个干吗？太令我伤心了
NO, YOU KNOW, THERE ARE PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD
要知道，这个世界上还是有这种人的
WHO GO ON FIRST DATES THAT ARE PERFECTLY GREAT,
在完美的约会之后
AND THEN THEY WAIT A WHILE BEFORE THEY ENGAGE
不会立即跟约会对象
IN SEXUAL CONTACT.
上床
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
恶心
I KNOW, I THINK IT ALL HAPPENS OUTSIDE OF NEW YORK.
不过我想，这种事都发生在纽约以外的地方吧
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
可能吧
WHEN HE TEXTS ME, IT'S LIKE HE ONLY TEXTS ME
他给我发短信的时候，
USING EMOTICONS.
永远都会用是表情符号
WHY CAN'T YOU USE YOUR WORDS?
他就不会打字吗？
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
你懂我的意思吧
I THINK THAT HE THINKS THAT THAT IS LIKE CUTE.
我猜他估计觉得这样很可爱
I AND LIKE...
我觉得